{"id": "152bd7bf-7164-45ef-990e-b06df7b7602b", "text_prompt": "There are 3 people: Grace, Nico, Jorge.\nThe attributes are: food: salad, sushi, pasta; sport: swimming, football, tennis.\nClues:\n- The person with sushi food doesn't have football sport.\n- Nico has pasta.\n- Grace doesn't have salad.\n- Nico doesn't have salad.\n- Jorge doesn't have swimming.\n- The person with tennis sport doesn't have pasta food.\n- Nico doesn't have swimming.\n\nDetermine which attributes correspond to each person.", "entities": ["Grace", "Nico", "Jorge"], "attributes": {"food": ["salad", "sushi", "pasta"], "sport": ["swimming", "football", "tennis"]}, "clues": [{"type": "eq", "entity": "Nico", "attr": "food", "value": "pasta"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Jorge", "attr": "sport", "value": "swimming"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Grace", "attr": "food", "value": "salad"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Nico", "attr": "food", "value": "salad"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Nico", "attr": "sport", "value": "swimming"}, {"type": "cross_neq", "attr1": "food", "value1": "sushi", "attr2": "sport", "value2": "football"}, {"type": "cross_neq", "attr1": "sport", "value1": "tennis", "attr2": "food", "value2": "pasta"}], "solution": {"Grace": {"food": "sushi", "sport": "swimming"}, "Nico": {"food": "pasta", "sport": "football"}, "Jorge": {"food": "salad", "sport": "tennis"}}}
{"id": "b344dee4-9d95-4005-bbb5-ddc4f5faeaf8", "text_prompt": "There are 3 people: Pablo, Nico, Bob.\nThe attributes are: drink: tea, water, coffee; sport: yoga, basketball, swimming.\nClues:\n- Bob doesn't have tea.\n- Nico doesn't have tea.\n- The person with basketball sport doesn't have water drink.\n- The person with yoga sport doesn't have tea drink.\n- Nico has swimming.\n- Nico doesn't have yoga.\n- Bob doesn't have water.\n\nDetermine which attributes correspond to each person.", "entities": ["Pablo", "Nico", "Bob"], "attributes": {"drink": ["tea", "water", "coffee"], "sport": ["yoga", "basketball", "swimming"]}, "clues": [{"type": "eq", "entity": "Nico", "attr": "sport", "value": "swimming"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Nico", "attr": "sport", "value": "yoga"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Bob", "attr": "drink", "value": "water"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Nico", "attr": "drink", "value": "tea"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Bob", "attr": "drink", "value": "tea"}, {"type": "cross_neq", "attr1": "sport", "value1": "basketball", "attr2": "drink", "value2": "water"}, {"type": "cross_neq", "attr1": "sport", "value1": "yoga", "attr2": "drink", "value2": "tea"}], "solution": {"Pablo": {"drink": "tea", "sport": "basketball"}, "Nico": {"drink": "water", "sport": "swimming"}, "Bob": {"drink": "coffee", "sport": "yoga"}}}
{"id": "66683c20-ec87-422b-9e35-f2651e1c2ff7", "text_prompt": "There are 3 people: Eva, Pablo, Bob.\nThe attributes are: sport: tennis, basketball, swimming; city: London, Paris, Rome.\nClues:\n- Bob has basketball.\n- Pablo doesn't have tennis.\n- Eva doesn't have Rome.\n- Eva doesn't have Paris.\n- Whoever has basketball sport has Rome city.\n- Pablo doesn't have London.\n- Whoever has Paris city has swimming sport.\n\nDetermine which attributes correspond to each person.", "entities": ["Eva", "Pablo", "Bob"], "attributes": {"sport": ["tennis", "basketball", "swimming"], "city": ["London", "Paris", "Rome"]}, "clues": [{"type": "eq", "entity": "Bob", "attr": "sport", "value": "basketball"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Pablo", "attr": "city", "value": "London"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Eva", "attr": "city", "value": "Paris"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Pablo", "attr": "sport", "value": "tennis"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Eva", "attr": "city", "value": "Rome"}, {"type": "cross_eq", "attr1": "city", "value1": "Paris", "attr2": "sport", "value2": "swimming"}, {"type": "cross_eq", "attr1": "sport", "value1": "basketball", "attr2": "city", "value2": "Rome"}], "solution": {"Eva": {"sport": "tennis", "city": "London"}, "Pablo": {"sport": "swimming", "city": "Paris"}, "Bob": {"sport": "basketball", "city": "Rome"}}}
{"id": "4fa1acd9-aa8e-4fc3-aa41-53b32cfac17f", "text_prompt": "There are 3 people: Carol, Nico, Eva.\nThe attributes are: drink: coffee, tea, juice; sport: tennis, basketball, football.\nClues:\n- Whoever has juice drink has football sport.\n- Carol has coffee.\n- Carol doesn't have basketball.\n- Carol doesn't have tea.\n- Eva doesn't have basketball.\n- Eva doesn't have tennis.\n- Whoever has coffee drink has tennis sport.\n\nDetermine which attributes correspond to each person.", "entities": ["Carol", "Nico", "Eva"], "attributes": {"drink": ["coffee", "tea", "juice"], "sport": ["tennis", "basketball", "football"]}, "clues": [{"type": "eq", "entity": "Carol", "attr": "drink", "value": "coffee"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Carol", "attr": "sport", "value": "basketball"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Carol", "attr": "drink", "value": "tea"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Eva", "attr": "sport", "value": "basketball"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Eva", "attr": "sport", "value": "tennis"}, {"type": "cross_eq", "attr1": "drink", "value1": "coffee", "attr2": "sport", "value2": "tennis"}, {"type": "cross_eq", "attr1": "drink", "value1": "juice", "attr2": "sport", "value2": "football"}], "solution": {"Carol": {"drink": "coffee", "sport": "tennis"}, "Nico": {"drink": "tea", "sport": "basketball"}, "Eva": {"drink": "juice", "sport": "football"}}}
{"id": "b63b914e-f9ac-442a-9843-0a359c8aea27", "text_prompt": "There are 3 people: Eva, Marta, Hugo.\nThe attributes are: animal: cat, hamster, fish; drink: coffee, tea, juice.\nClues:\n- Marta doesn't have juice.\n- Hugo has fish.\n- Eva doesn't have juice.\n- Hugo doesn't have tea.\n- Whoever has hamster animal has tea drink.\n- Whoever has tea drink has hamster animal.\n- Marta doesn't have coffee.\n\nDetermine which attributes correspond to each person.", "entities": ["Eva", "Marta", "Hugo"], "attributes": {"animal": ["cat", "hamster", "fish"], "drink": ["coffee", "tea", "juice"]}, "clues": [{"type": "eq", "entity": "Hugo", "attr": "animal", "value": "fish"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Eva", "attr": "drink", "value": "juice"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Marta", "attr": "drink", "value": "juice"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Hugo", "attr": "drink", "value": "tea"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Marta", "attr": "drink", "value": "coffee"}, {"type": "cross_eq", "attr1": "animal", "value1": "hamster", "attr2": "drink", "value2": "tea"}, {"type": "cross_eq", "attr1": "drink", "value1": "tea", "attr2": "animal", "value2": "hamster"}], "solution": {"Eva": {"animal": "cat", "drink": "coffee"}, "Marta": {"animal": "hamster", "drink": "tea"}, "Hugo": {"animal": "fish", "drink": "juice"}}}
{"id": "f2ab7eeb-1852-4d43-8755-ef5718c02a7e", "text_prompt": "There are 3 people: Frank, David, Quinn.\nThe attributes are: animal: bird, hamster, fish; drink: coffee, juice, soda.\nClues:\n- The person with fish animal doesn't have soda drink.\n- Quinn doesn't have coffee.\n- Quinn doesn't have soda.\n- Frank doesn't have fish.\n- The person with hamster animal doesn't have soda drink.\n- Quinn doesn't have bird.\n- David has bird.\n\nDetermine which attributes correspond to each person.", "entities": ["Frank", "David", "Quinn"], "attributes": {"animal": ["bird", "hamster", "fish"], "drink": ["coffee", "juice", "soda"]}, "clues": [{"type": "eq", "entity": "David", "attr": "animal", "value": "bird"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Frank", "attr": "animal", "value": "fish"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Quinn", "attr": "animal", "value": "bird"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Quinn", "attr": "drink", "value": "coffee"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Quinn", "attr": "drink", "value": "soda"}, {"type": "cross_neq", "attr1": "animal", "value1": "fish", "attr2": "drink", "value2": "soda"}, {"type": "cross_neq", "attr1": "animal", "value1": "hamster", "attr2": "drink", "value2": "soda"}], "solution": {"Frank": {"animal": "hamster", "drink": "coffee"}, "David": {"animal": "bird", "drink": "soda"}, "Quinn": {"animal": "fish", "drink": "juice"}}}
{"id": "b8eec23b-721a-44e4-8f69-631fea940a48", "text_prompt": "There are 3 people: Marta, David, Jorge.\nThe attributes are: drink: soda, coffee, tea; animal: fish, dog, bird.\nClues:\n- Whoever has bird animal has tea drink.\n- Jorge has fish.\n- Marta doesn't have dog.\n- Marta doesn't have coffee.\n- Marta doesn't have soda.\n- The person with coffee drink doesn't have bird animal.\n- Jorge doesn't have coffee.\n\nDetermine which attributes correspond to each person.", "entities": ["Marta", "David", "Jorge"], "attributes": {"drink": ["soda", "coffee", "tea"], "animal": ["fish", "dog", "bird"]}, "clues": [{"type": "eq", "entity": "Jorge", "attr": "animal", "value": "fish"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Jorge", "attr": "drink", "value": "coffee"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Marta", "attr": "drink", "value": "soda"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Marta", "attr": "animal", "value": "dog"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Marta", "attr": "drink", "value": "coffee"}, {"type": "cross_eq", "attr1": "animal", "value1": "bird", "attr2": "drink", "value2": "tea"}, {"type": "cross_neq", "attr1": "drink", "value1": "coffee", "attr2": "animal", "value2": "bird"}], "solution": {"Marta": {"drink": "tea", "animal": "bird"}, "David": {"drink": "coffee", "animal": "dog"}, "Jorge": {"drink": "soda", "animal": "fish"}}}
{"id": "ba10f4ca-c3a0-46c6-b3ed-b0eafd460373", "text_prompt": "There are 3 people: Grace, Frank, Pablo.\nThe attributes are: food: salad, tacos, pasta; animal: hamster, fish, bird.\nClues:\n- Frank doesn't have fish.\n- Whoever has salad food has bird animal.\n- Pablo has tacos.\n- Grace doesn't have pasta.\n- Whoever has pasta food has hamster animal.\n- Pablo doesn't have salad.\n- Pablo doesn't have pasta.\n\nDetermine which attributes correspond to each person.", "entities": ["Grace", "Frank", "Pablo"], "attributes": {"food": ["salad", "tacos", "pasta"], "animal": ["hamster", "fish", "bird"]}, "clues": [{"type": "eq", "entity": "Pablo", "attr": "food", "value": "tacos"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Pablo", "attr": "food", "value": "pasta"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Frank", "attr": "animal", "value": "fish"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Pablo", "attr": "food", "value": "salad"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Grace", "attr": "food", "value": "pasta"}, {"type": "cross_eq", "attr1": "food", "value1": "pasta", "attr2": "animal", "value2": "hamster"}, {"type": "cross_eq", "attr1": "food", "value1": "salad", "attr2": "animal", "value2": "bird"}], "solution": {"Grace": {"food": "salad", "animal": "bird"}, "Frank": {"food": "pasta", "animal": "hamster"}, "Pablo": {"food": "tacos", "animal": "fish"}}}
{"id": "005c7bab-e894-4ad6-a9fb-03665c601175", "text_prompt": "There are 3 people: Hugo, David, Nico.\nThe attributes are: food: tacos, salad, sushi; sport: yoga, tennis, swimming.\nClues:\n- Nico doesn't have yoga.\n- Hugo doesn't have yoga.\n- David doesn't have tacos.\n- Hugo doesn't have tennis.\n- The person with swimming sport doesn't have salad food.\n- Nico has sushi.\n- Whoever has salad food has yoga sport.\n\nDetermine which attributes correspond to each person.", "entities": ["Hugo", "David", "Nico"], "attributes": {"food": ["tacos", "salad", "sushi"], "sport": ["yoga", "tennis", "swimming"]}, "clues": [{"type": "eq", "entity": "Nico", "attr": "food", "value": "sushi"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Hugo", "attr": "sport", "value": "tennis"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "David", "attr": "food", "value": "tacos"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Hugo", "attr": "sport", "value": "yoga"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Nico", "attr": "sport", "value": "yoga"}, {"type": "cross_neq", "attr1": "sport", "value1": "swimming", "attr2": "food", "value2": "salad"}, {"type": "cross_eq", "attr1": "food", "value1": "salad", "attr2": "sport", "value2": "yoga"}], "solution": {"Hugo": {"food": "tacos", "sport": "swimming"}, "David": {"food": "salad", "sport": "yoga"}, "Nico": {"food": "sushi", "sport": "tennis"}}}
{"id": "43bb5586-de5f-4a0e-a09f-626a43ab5615", "text_prompt": "There are 3 people: Jorge, Eva, Nico.\nThe attributes are: food: salad, pasta, sushi; sport: yoga, football, swimming.\nClues:\n- Eva doesn't have yoga.\n- Jorge has football.\n- Nico doesn't have pasta.\n- Eva doesn't have sushi.\n- Whoever has sushi food has football sport.\n- Eva doesn't have salad.\n- Whoever has salad food has yoga sport.\n\nDetermine which attributes correspond to each person.", "entities": ["Jorge", "Eva", "Nico"], "attributes": {"food": ["salad", "pasta", "sushi"], "sport": ["yoga", "football", "swimming"]}, "clues": [{"type": "eq", "entity": "Jorge", "attr": "sport", "value": "football"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Eva", "attr": "food", "value": "sushi"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Eva", "attr": "sport", "value": "yoga"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Eva", "attr": "food", "value": "salad"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Nico", "attr": "food", "value": "pasta"}, {"type": "cross_eq", "attr1": "food", "value1": "sushi", "attr2": "sport", "value2": "football"}, {"type": "cross_eq", "attr1": "food", "value1": "salad", "attr2": "sport", "value2": "yoga"}], "solution": {"Jorge": {"food": "sushi", "sport": "football"}, "Eva": {"food": "pasta", "sport": "swimming"}, "Nico": {"food": "salad", "sport": "yoga"}}}
{"id": "98517246-777b-4f4c-8956-74ac5ebd687b", "text_prompt": "There are 3 people: Jorge, Alice, Sara.\nThe attributes are: food: tacos, sushi, salad; city: Berlin, London, Paris.\nClues:\n- Alice has Berlin.\n- Sara doesn't have Paris.\n- Sara doesn't have Berlin.\n- Whoever has sushi food has London city.\n- Jorge doesn't have salad.\n- Whoever has tacos food has Paris city.\n- Alice doesn't have Paris.\n\nDetermine which attributes correspond to each person.", "entities": ["Jorge", "Alice", "Sara"], "attributes": {"food": ["tacos", "sushi", "salad"], "city": ["Berlin", "London", "Paris"]}, "clues": [{"type": "eq", "entity": "Alice", "attr": "city", "value": "Berlin"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Sara", "attr": "city", "value": "Berlin"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Jorge", "attr": "food", "value": "salad"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Sara", "attr": "city", "value": "Paris"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Alice", "attr": "city", "value": "Paris"}, {"type": "cross_eq", "attr1": "food", "value1": "tacos", "attr2": "city", "value2": "Paris"}, {"type": "cross_eq", "attr1": "food", "value1": "sushi", "attr2": "city", "value2": "London"}], "solution": {"Jorge": {"food": "tacos", "city": "Paris"}, "Alice": {"food": "salad", "city": "Berlin"}, "Sara": {"food": "sushi", "city": "London"}}}
{"id": "b98f1036-72df-4d74-92c8-b741504312d5", "text_prompt": "There are 3 people: Frank, Alice, Nico.\nThe attributes are: food: tacos, salad, pasta; sport: tennis, yoga, swimming.\nClues:\n- Frank doesn't have yoga.\n- Nico doesn't have tacos.\n- Alice doesn't have yoga.\n- The person with swimming sport doesn't have salad food.\n- The person with pasta food doesn't have swimming sport.\n- Nico doesn't have pasta.\n- Alice has swimming.\n\nDetermine which attributes correspond to each person.", "entities": ["Frank", "Alice", "Nico"], "attributes": {"food": ["tacos", "salad", "pasta"], "sport": ["tennis", "yoga", "swimming"]}, "clues": [{"type": "eq", "entity": "Alice", "attr": "sport", "value": "swimming"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Nico", "attr": "food", "value": "tacos"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Frank", "attr": "sport", "value": "yoga"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Nico", "attr": "food", "value": "pasta"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Alice", "attr": "sport", "value": "yoga"}, {"type": "cross_neq", "attr1": "sport", "value1": "swimming", "attr2": "food", "value2": "salad"}, {"type": "cross_neq", "attr1": "food", "value1": "pasta", "attr2": "sport", "value2": "swimming"}], "solution": {"Frank": {"food": "pasta", "sport": "tennis"}, "Alice": {"food": "tacos", "sport": "swimming"}, "Nico": {"food": "salad", "sport": "yoga"}}}
{"id": "aa5fcae0-934b-4eb1-a14b-7bb40600b23e", "text_prompt": "There are 3 people: Eva, Hugo, Quinn.\nThe attributes are: city: Madrid, Berlin, Paris; food: sushi, pizza, salad.\nClues:\n- Whoever has Madrid city has pizza food.\n- Quinn doesn't have Madrid.\n- Hugo has Paris.\n- Whoever has Berlin city has sushi food.\n- Hugo doesn't have pizza.\n- Quinn doesn't have Paris.\n- Eva doesn't have Paris.\n\nDetermine which attributes correspond to each person.", "entities": ["Eva", "Hugo", "Quinn"], "attributes": {"city": ["Madrid", "Berlin", "Paris"], "food": ["sushi", "pizza", "salad"]}, "clues": [{"type": "eq", "entity": "Hugo", "attr": "city", "value": "Paris"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Quinn", "attr": "city", "value": "Paris"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Eva", "attr": "city", "value": "Paris"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Quinn", "attr": "city", "value": "Madrid"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Hugo", "attr": "food", "value": "pizza"}, {"type": "cross_eq", "attr1": "city", "value1": "Madrid", "attr2": "food", "value2": "pizza"}, {"type": "cross_eq", "attr1": "city", "value1": "Berlin", "attr2": "food", "value2": "sushi"}], "solution": {"Eva": {"city": "Madrid", "food": "pizza"}, "Hugo": {"city": "Paris", "food": "salad"}, "Quinn": {"city": "Berlin", "food": "sushi"}}}
{"id": "9197daee-045c-4755-ad81-f5c02263a58f", "text_prompt": "There are 3 people: Jorge, Vera, Irene.\nThe attributes are: animal: hamster, dog, fish; sport: football, swimming, basketball.\nClues:\n- Whoever has hamster animal has football sport.\n- Irene doesn't have swimming.\n- Jorge doesn't have hamster.\n- Vera doesn't have basketball.\n- Whoever has football sport has hamster animal.\n- Irene has dog.\n- Irene doesn't have hamster.\n\nDetermine which attributes correspond to each person.", "entities": ["Jorge", "Vera", "Irene"], "attributes": {"animal": ["hamster", "dog", "fish"], "sport": ["football", "swimming", "basketball"]}, "clues": [{"type": "eq", "entity": "Irene", "attr": "animal", "value": "dog"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Vera", "attr": "sport", "value": "basketball"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Jorge", "attr": "animal", "value": "hamster"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Irene", "attr": "sport", "value": "swimming"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Irene", "attr": "animal", "value": "hamster"}, {"type": "cross_eq", "attr1": "sport", "value1": "football", "attr2": "animal", "value2": "hamster"}, {"type": "cross_eq", "attr1": "animal", "value1": "hamster", "attr2": "sport", "value2": "football"}], "solution": {"Jorge": {"animal": "fish", "sport": "swimming"}, "Vera": {"animal": "hamster", "sport": "football"}, "Irene": {"animal": "dog", "sport": "basketball"}}}
{"id": "3f8348c1-6170-44ec-a9c6-6a32d8ac454a", "text_prompt": "There are 3 people: Bob, Marta, Carol.\nThe attributes are: drink: coffee, soda, juice; city: Berlin, London, Madrid.\nClues:\n- Marta has Madrid.\n- Bob doesn't have Madrid.\n- The person with soda drink doesn't have Berlin city.\n- The person with Berlin city doesn't have soda drink.\n- Bob doesn't have coffee.\n- Carol doesn't have coffee.\n- Carol doesn't have London.\n\nDetermine which attributes correspond to each person.", "entities": ["Bob", "Marta", "Carol"], "attributes": {"drink": ["coffee", "soda", "juice"], "city": ["Berlin", "London", "Madrid"]}, "clues": [{"type": "eq", "entity": "Marta", "attr": "city", "value": "Madrid"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Carol", "attr": "city", "value": "London"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Bob", "attr": "city", "value": "Madrid"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Bob", "attr": "drink", "value": "coffee"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Carol", "attr": "drink", "value": "coffee"}, {"type": "cross_neq", "attr1": "drink", "value1": "soda", "attr2": "city", "value2": "Berlin"}, {"type": "cross_neq", "attr1": "city", "value1": "Berlin", "attr2": "drink", "value2": "soda"}], "solution": {"Bob": {"drink": "soda", "city": "London"}, "Marta": {"drink": "coffee", "city": "Madrid"}, "Carol": {"drink": "juice", "city": "Berlin"}}}
{"id": "96cd79b4-c9c4-4c5c-92c4-54ed7c22f0c6", "text_prompt": "There are 3 people: Alice, Frank, Vera.\nThe attributes are: color: yellow, red, blue; animal: fish, cat, bird.\nClues:\n- Vera doesn't have cat.\n- Whoever has blue color has bird animal.\n- Whoever has yellow color has fish animal.\n- Vera doesn't have red.\n- Frank has fish.\n- Alice doesn't have fish.\n- Frank doesn't have red.\n\nDetermine which attributes correspond to each person.", "entities": ["Alice", "Frank", "Vera"], "attributes": {"color": ["yellow", "red", "blue"], "animal": ["fish", "cat", "bird"]}, "clues": [{"type": "eq", "entity": "Frank", "attr": "animal", "value": "fish"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Vera", "attr": "animal", "value": "cat"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Vera", "attr": "color", "value": "red"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Alice", "attr": "animal", "value": "fish"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Frank", "attr": "color", "value": "red"}, {"type": "cross_eq", "attr1": "color", "value1": "yellow", "attr2": "animal", "value2": "fish"}, {"type": "cross_eq", "attr1": "color", "value1": "blue", "attr2": "animal", "value2": "bird"}], "solution": {"Alice": {"color": "red", "animal": "cat"}, "Frank": {"color": "yellow", "animal": "fish"}, "Vera": {"color": "blue", "animal": "bird"}}}
{"id": "96984353-5a7f-496e-a5f1-2e3d83182190", "text_prompt": "There are 3 people: Jorge, Sara, Irene.\nThe attributes are: drink: soda, coffee, water; animal: dog, hamster, bird.\nClues:\n- Irene doesn't have water.\n- Sara has dog.\n- Sara doesn't have water.\n- Sara doesn't have hamster.\n- The person with soda drink doesn't have hamster animal.\n- Whoever has dog animal has coffee drink.\n- Irene doesn't have hamster.\n\nDetermine which attributes correspond to each person.", "entities": ["Jorge", "Sara", "Irene"], "attributes": {"drink": ["soda", "coffee", "water"], "animal": ["dog", "hamster", "bird"]}, "clues": [{"type": "eq", "entity": "Sara", "attr": "animal", "value": "dog"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Sara", "attr": "animal", "value": "hamster"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Sara", "attr": "drink", "value": "water"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Irene", "attr": "drink", "value": "water"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Irene", "attr": "animal", "value": "hamster"}, {"type": "cross_neq", "attr1": "drink", "value1": "soda", "attr2": "animal", "value2": "hamster"}, {"type": "cross_eq", "attr1": "animal", "value1": "dog", "attr2": "drink", "value2": "coffee"}], "solution": {"Jorge": {"drink": "water", "animal": "hamster"}, "Sara": {"drink": "coffee", "animal": "dog"}, "Irene": {"drink": "soda", "animal": "bird"}}}
{"id": "a2dd6368-248e-40a5-aa01-782e01bb6e80", "text_prompt": "There are 3 people: Eva, Pablo, Irene.\nThe attributes are: color: yellow, green, red; city: Berlin, Paris, Rome.\nClues:\n- Eva has yellow.\n- Whoever has Rome city has red color.\n- Eva doesn't have green.\n- Whoever has Berlin city has yellow color.\n- Pablo doesn't have green.\n- Pablo doesn't have Paris.\n- Eva doesn't have Paris.\n\nDetermine which attributes correspond to each person.", "entities": ["Eva", "Pablo", "Irene"], "attributes": {"color": ["yellow", "green", "red"], "city": ["Berlin", "Paris", "Rome"]}, "clues": [{"type": "eq", "entity": "Eva", "attr": "color", "value": "yellow"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Pablo", "attr": "color", "value": "green"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Eva", "attr": "color", "value": "green"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Eva", "attr": "city", "value": "Paris"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Pablo", "attr": "city", "value": "Paris"}, {"type": "cross_eq", "attr1": "city", "value1": "Berlin", "attr2": "color", "value2": "yellow"}, {"type": "cross_eq", "attr1": "city", "value1": "Rome", "attr2": "color", "value2": "red"}], "solution": {"Eva": {"color": "yellow", "city": "Berlin"}, "Pablo": {"color": "red", "city": "Rome"}, "Irene": {"color": "green", "city": "Paris"}}}
{"id": "5ffc74fd-6bb5-4575-ad40-37702f58acde", "text_prompt": "There are 3 people: Alice, David, Pablo.\nThe attributes are: drink: soda, coffee, juice; sport: basketball, tennis, yoga.\nClues:\n- Whoever has soda drink has yoga sport.\n- David doesn't have yoga.\n- Pablo has juice.\n- Whoever has yoga sport has soda drink.\n- Alice doesn't have tennis.\n- Pablo doesn't have basketball.\n- Alice doesn't have coffee.\n\nDetermine which attributes correspond to each person.", "entities": ["Alice", "David", "Pablo"], "attributes": {"drink": ["soda", "coffee", "juice"], "sport": ["basketball", "tennis", "yoga"]}, "clues": [{"type": "eq", "entity": "Pablo", "attr": "drink", "value": "juice"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "David", "attr": "sport", "value": "yoga"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Alice", "attr": "sport", "value": "tennis"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Alice", "attr": "drink", "value": "coffee"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Pablo", "attr": "sport", "value": "basketball"}, {"type": "cross_eq", "attr1": "sport", "value1": "yoga", "attr2": "drink", "value2": "soda"}, {"type": "cross_eq", "attr1": "drink", "value1": "soda", "attr2": "sport", "value2": "yoga"}], "solution": {"Alice": {"drink": "soda", "sport": "yoga"}, "David": {"drink": "coffee", "sport": "basketball"}, "Pablo": {"drink": "juice", "sport": "tennis"}}}
{"id": "7d2ba6ec-fef7-45f4-9711-7bb8f19f183a", "text_prompt": "There are 3 people: Bob, Olga, Sara.\nThe attributes are: drink: water, juice, coffee; sport: basketball, yoga, swimming.\nClues:\n- Sara doesn't have basketball.\n- Olga doesn't have juice.\n- Sara doesn't have swimming.\n- Bob has water.\n- Bob doesn't have yoga.\n- Whoever has basketball sport has coffee drink.\n- Whoever has swimming sport has water drink.\n\nDetermine which attributes correspond to each person.", "entities": ["Bob", "Olga", "Sara"], "attributes": {"drink": ["water", "juice", "coffee"], "sport": ["basketball", "yoga", "swimming"]}, "clues": [{"type": "eq", "entity": "Bob", "attr": "drink", "value": "water"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Olga", "attr": "drink", "value": "juice"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Sara", "attr": "sport", "value": "basketball"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Bob", "attr": "sport", "value": "yoga"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Sara", "attr": "sport", "value": "swimming"}, {"type": "cross_eq", "attr1": "sport", "value1": "swimming", "attr2": "drink", "value2": "water"}, {"type": "cross_eq", "attr1": "sport", "value1": "basketball", "attr2": "drink", "value2": "coffee"}], "solution": {"Bob": {"drink": "water", "sport": "swimming"}, "Olga": {"drink": "coffee", "sport": "basketball"}, "Sara": {"drink": "juice", "sport": "yoga"}}}
{"id": "11a7a6be-997b-4330-a955-c119c0b82a2c", "text_prompt": "There are 3 people: Hugo, Vera, Bob.\nThe attributes are: color: blue, green, red; drink: water, coffee, tea.\nClues:\n- Hugo has red.\n- Vera doesn't have coffee.\n- Whoever has red color has tea drink.\n- Bob doesn't have tea.\n- Vera doesn't have tea.\n- Bob doesn't have water.\n- Whoever has coffee drink has green color.\n\nDetermine which attributes correspond to each person.", "entities": ["Hugo", "Vera", "Bob"], "attributes": {"color": ["blue", "green", "red"], "drink": ["water", "coffee", "tea"]}, "clues": [{"type": "eq", "entity": "Hugo", "attr": "color", "value": "red"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Vera", "attr": "drink", "value": "tea"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Vera", "attr": "drink", "value": "coffee"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Bob", "attr": "drink", "value": "water"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Bob", "attr": "drink", "value": "tea"}, {"type": "cross_eq", "attr1": "color", "value1": "red", "attr2": "drink", "value2": "tea"}, {"type": "cross_eq", "attr1": "drink", "value1": "coffee", "attr2": "color", "value2": "green"}], "solution": {"Hugo": {"color": "red", "drink": "tea"}, "Vera": {"color": "blue", "drink": "water"}, "Bob": {"color": "green", "drink": "coffee"}}}
{"id": "2b0025a3-f8ea-44cc-8e3d-83bdd4182074", "text_prompt": "There are 3 people: Irene, Alice, Quinn.\nThe attributes are: drink: water, coffee, tea; city: Paris, Rome, Berlin.\nClues:\n- Whoever has Rome city has water drink.\n- Quinn has Rome.\n- Alice doesn't have water.\n- Quinn doesn't have tea.\n- The person with tea drink doesn't have Rome city.\n- Irene doesn't have Paris.\n- Irene doesn't have coffee.\n\nDetermine which attributes correspond to each person.", "entities": ["Irene", "Alice", "Quinn"], "attributes": {"drink": ["water", "coffee", "tea"], "city": ["Paris", "Rome", "Berlin"]}, "clues": [{"type": "eq", "entity": "Quinn", "attr": "city", "value": "Rome"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Quinn", "attr": "drink", "value": "tea"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Alice", "attr": "drink", "value": "water"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Irene", "attr": "city", "value": "Paris"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Irene", "attr": "drink", "value": "coffee"}, {"type": "cross_neq", "attr1": "drink", "value1": "tea", "attr2": "city", "value2": "Rome"}, {"type": "cross_eq", "attr1": "city", "value1": "Rome", "attr2": "drink", "value2": "water"}], "solution": {"Irene": {"drink": "tea", "city": "Berlin"}, "Alice": {"drink": "coffee", "city": "Paris"}, "Quinn": {"drink": "water", "city": "Rome"}}}
{"id": "a4751c4e-baa6-416c-bad2-88798710dda0", "text_prompt": "There are 3 people: Alice, Vera, Quinn.\nThe attributes are: food: sushi, pizza, pasta; sport: tennis, yoga, basketball.\nClues:\n- Alice doesn't have tennis.\n- Vera doesn't have sushi.\n- Whoever has basketball sport has pasta food.\n- Quinn doesn't have tennis.\n- Vera doesn't have yoga.\n- Quinn has pasta.\n- Whoever has tennis sport has pizza food.\n\nDetermine which attributes correspond to each person.", "entities": ["Alice", "Vera", "Quinn"], "attributes": {"food": ["sushi", "pizza", "pasta"], "sport": ["tennis", "yoga", "basketball"]}, "clues": [{"type": "eq", "entity": "Quinn", "attr": "food", "value": "pasta"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Quinn", "attr": "sport", "value": "tennis"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Vera", "attr": "food", "value": "sushi"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Alice", "attr": "sport", "value": "tennis"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Vera", "attr": "sport", "value": "yoga"}, {"type": "cross_eq", "attr1": "sport", "value1": "tennis", "attr2": "food", "value2": "pizza"}, {"type": "cross_eq", "attr1": "sport", "value1": "basketball", "attr2": "food", "value2": "pasta"}], "solution": {"Alice": {"food": "sushi", "sport": "yoga"}, "Vera": {"food": "pizza", "sport": "tennis"}, "Quinn": {"food": "pasta", "sport": "basketball"}}}
{"id": "6792aa08-4e6f-4ad0-9840-98034a1cbb53", "text_prompt": "There are 3 people: Nico, Pablo, Eva.\nThe attributes are: food: salad, pasta, sushi; city: Rome, Madrid, London.\nClues:\n- Nico doesn't have sushi.\n- Whoever has Rome city has pasta food.\n- Pablo doesn't have Madrid.\n- Whoever has London city has sushi food.\n- Nico has Rome.\n- Eva doesn't have pasta.\n- Nico doesn't have London.\n\nDetermine which attributes correspond to each person.", "entities": ["Nico", "Pablo", "Eva"], "attributes": {"food": ["salad", "pasta", "sushi"], "city": ["Rome", "Madrid", "London"]}, "clues": [{"type": "eq", "entity": "Nico", "attr": "city", "value": "Rome"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Eva", "attr": "food", "value": "pasta"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Nico", "attr": "food", "value": "sushi"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Pablo", "attr": "city", "value": "Madrid"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Nico", "attr": "city", "value": "London"}, {"type": "cross_eq", "attr1": "city", "value1": "Rome", "attr2": "food", "value2": "pasta"}, {"type": "cross_eq", "attr1": "city", "value1": "London", "attr2": "food", "value2": "sushi"}], "solution": {"Nico": {"food": "pasta", "city": "Rome"}, "Pablo": {"food": "sushi", "city": "London"}, "Eva": {"food": "salad", "city": "Madrid"}}}
{"id": "dc739379-13fd-47cc-9750-f723a84742d3", "text_prompt": "There are 3 people: Bob, David, Irene.\nThe attributes are: animal: fish, hamster, dog; city: Rome, Paris, Madrid.\nClues:\n- Irene doesn't have Madrid.\n- Bob has Madrid.\n- Bob doesn't have dog.\n- David doesn't have Paris.\n- Whoever has Madrid city has hamster animal.\n- Irene doesn't have fish.\n- Whoever has hamster animal has Madrid city.\n\nDetermine which attributes correspond to each person.", "entities": ["Bob", "David", "Irene"], "attributes": {"animal": ["fish", "hamster", "dog"], "city": ["Rome", "Paris", "Madrid"]}, "clues": [{"type": "eq", "entity": "Bob", "attr": "city", "value": "Madrid"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Bob", "attr": "animal", "value": "dog"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "David", "attr": "city", "value": "Paris"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Irene", "attr": "city", "value": "Madrid"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Irene", "attr": "animal", "value": "fish"}, {"type": "cross_eq", "attr1": "city", "value1": "Madrid", "attr2": "animal", "value2": "hamster"}, {"type": "cross_eq", "attr1": "animal", "value1": "hamster", "attr2": "city", "value2": "Madrid"}], "solution": {"Bob": {"animal": "hamster", "city": "Madrid"}, "David": {"animal": "fish", "city": "Rome"}, "Irene": {"animal": "dog", "city": "Paris"}}}
{"id": "08fdfd07-9764-4608-8c9a-a0bf6d3254d8", "text_prompt": "There are 3 people: Vera, Eva, Irene.\nThe attributes are: animal: hamster, fish, bird; food: salad, tacos, pasta.\nClues:\n- Whoever has tacos food has fish animal.\n- Irene doesn't have hamster.\n- Whoever has bird animal has pasta food.\n- Irene doesn't have tacos.\n- Eva has hamster.\n- Eva doesn't have bird.\n- Eva doesn't have tacos.\n\nDetermine which attributes correspond to each person.", "entities": ["Vera", "Eva", "Irene"], "attributes": {"animal": ["hamster", "fish", "bird"], "food": ["salad", "tacos", "pasta"]}, "clues": [{"type": "eq", "entity": "Eva", "attr": "animal", "value": "hamster"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Eva", "attr": "food", "value": "tacos"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Irene", "attr": "animal", "value": "hamster"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Eva", "attr": "animal", "value": "bird"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Irene", "attr": "food", "value": "tacos"}, {"type": "cross_eq", "attr1": "food", "value1": "tacos", "attr2": "animal", "value2": "fish"}, {"type": "cross_eq", "attr1": "animal", "value1": "bird", "attr2": "food", "value2": "pasta"}], "solution": {"Vera": {"animal": "fish", "food": "tacos"}, "Eva": {"animal": "hamster", "food": "salad"}, "Irene": {"animal": "bird", "food": "pasta"}}}
{"id": "2ae3ab05-912d-4a83-a129-acfab02de053", "text_prompt": "There are 3 people: Alice, Bob, Irene.\nThe attributes are: animal: cat, dog, hamster; color: purple, blue, yellow.\nClues:\n- Alice doesn't have blue.\n- The person with blue color doesn't have dog animal.\n- Alice has dog.\n- Bob doesn't have cat.\n- Alice doesn't have purple.\n- Whoever has dog animal has yellow color.\n- Irene doesn't have blue.\n\nDetermine which attributes correspond to each person.", "entities": ["Alice", "Bob", "Irene"], "attributes": {"animal": ["cat", "dog", "hamster"], "color": ["purple", "blue", "yellow"]}, "clues": [{"type": "eq", "entity": "Alice", "attr": "animal", "value": "dog"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Irene", "attr": "color", "value": "blue"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Alice", "attr": "color", "value": "blue"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Bob", "attr": "animal", "value": "cat"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Alice", "attr": "color", "value": "purple"}, {"type": "cross_eq", "attr1": "animal", "value1": "dog", "attr2": "color", "value2": "yellow"}, {"type": "cross_neq", "attr1": "color", "value1": "blue", "attr2": "animal", "value2": "dog"}], "solution": {"Alice": {"animal": "dog", "color": "yellow"}, "Bob": {"animal": "hamster", "color": "blue"}, "Irene": {"animal": "cat", "color": "purple"}}}
{"id": "96a02426-9d07-40eb-99c7-07408a3ab40a", "text_prompt": "There are 3 people: Hugo, Irene, Olga.\nThe attributes are: food: sushi, salad, tacos; drink: soda, juice, coffee.\nClues:\n- Hugo doesn't have salad.\n- Whoever has sushi food has soda drink.\n- Irene doesn't have salad.\n- Hugo doesn't have coffee.\n- Hugo doesn't have sushi.\n- Irene has sushi.\n- The person with soda drink doesn't have tacos food.\n\nDetermine which attributes correspond to each person.", "entities": ["Hugo", "Irene", "Olga"], "attributes": {"food": ["sushi", "salad", "tacos"], "drink": ["soda", "juice", "coffee"]}, "clues": [{"type": "eq", "entity": "Irene", "attr": "food", "value": "sushi"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Hugo", "attr": "food", "value": "salad"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Hugo", "attr": "drink", "value": "coffee"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Irene", "attr": "food", "value": "salad"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Hugo", "attr": "food", "value": "sushi"}, {"type": "cross_neq", "attr1": "drink", "value1": "soda", "attr2": "food", "value2": "tacos"}, {"type": "cross_eq", "attr1": "food", "value1": "sushi", "attr2": "drink", "value2": "soda"}], "solution": {"Hugo": {"food": "tacos", "drink": "juice"}, "Irene": {"food": "sushi", "drink": "soda"}, "Olga": {"food": "salad", "drink": "coffee"}}}
{"id": "1bfd4e3d-915d-4731-833c-e66afbbdc589", "text_prompt": "There are 3 people: Eva, Carol, Frank.\nThe attributes are: sport: swimming, basketball, football; food: pasta, pizza, tacos.\nClues:\n- The person with pizza food doesn't have swimming sport.\n- Eva doesn't have pasta.\n- Frank doesn't have pasta.\n- Carol has basketball.\n- Carol doesn't have tacos.\n- Whoever has swimming sport has tacos food.\n- Frank doesn't have football.\n\nDetermine which attributes correspond to each person.", "entities": ["Eva", "Carol", "Frank"], "attributes": {"sport": ["swimming", "basketball", "football"], "food": ["pasta", "pizza", "tacos"]}, "clues": [{"type": "eq", "entity": "Carol", "attr": "sport", "value": "basketball"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Carol", "attr": "food", "value": "tacos"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Frank", "attr": "food", "value": "pasta"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Eva", "attr": "food", "value": "pasta"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Frank", "attr": "sport", "value": "football"}, {"type": "cross_eq", "attr1": "sport", "value1": "swimming", "attr2": "food", "value2": "tacos"}, {"type": "cross_neq", "attr1": "food", "value1": "pizza", "attr2": "sport", "value2": "swimming"}], "solution": {"Eva": {"sport": "football", "food": "pizza"}, "Carol": {"sport": "basketball", "food": "pasta"}, "Frank": {"sport": "swimming", "food": "tacos"}}}
{"id": "8fd0cecb-a3c0-43cf-8cff-adb24b98b3bf", "text_prompt": "There are 3 people: Nico, Irene, Olga.\nThe attributes are: drink: juice, water, tea; food: tacos, salad, sushi.\nClues:\n- Irene has sushi.\n- Olga doesn't have juice.\n- Nico doesn't have salad.\n- The person with salad food doesn't have water drink.\n- Irene doesn't have tea.\n- Nico doesn't have water.\n- The person with tacos food doesn't have water drink.\n\nDetermine which attributes correspond to each person.", "entities": ["Nico", "Irene", "Olga"], "attributes": {"drink": ["juice", "water", "tea"], "food": ["tacos", "salad", "sushi"]}, "clues": [{"type": "eq", "entity": "Irene", "attr": "food", "value": "sushi"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Nico", "attr": "drink", "value": "water"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Nico", "attr": "food", "value": "salad"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Irene", "attr": "drink", "value": "tea"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Olga", "attr": "drink", "value": "juice"}, {"type": "cross_neq", "attr1": "food", "value1": "tacos", "attr2": "drink", "value2": "water"}, {"type": "cross_neq", "attr1": "food", "value1": "salad", "attr2": "drink", "value2": "water"}], "solution": {"Nico": {"drink": "juice", "food": "tacos"}, "Irene": {"drink": "water", "food": "sushi"}, "Olga": {"drink": "tea", "food": "salad"}}}
{"id": "324e4511-6cf5-4937-a135-f6b99ee5819c", "text_prompt": "There are 3 people: Carol, Bob, Grace.\nThe attributes are: food: pasta, tacos, sushi; color: green, purple, yellow.\nClues:\n- Carol doesn't have sushi.\n- Grace has pasta.\n- Bob doesn't have purple.\n- Whoever has yellow color has tacos food.\n- Whoever has purple color has pasta food.\n- Carol doesn't have pasta.\n- Grace doesn't have yellow.\n\nDetermine which attributes correspond to each person.", "entities": ["Carol", "Bob", "Grace"], "attributes": {"food": ["pasta", "tacos", "sushi"], "color": ["green", "purple", "yellow"]}, "clues": [{"type": "eq", "entity": "Grace", "attr": "food", "value": "pasta"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Grace", "attr": "color", "value": "yellow"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Bob", "attr": "color", "value": "purple"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Carol", "attr": "food", "value": "pasta"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Carol", "attr": "food", "value": "sushi"}, {"type": "cross_eq", "attr1": "color", "value1": "purple", "attr2": "food", "value2": "pasta"}, {"type": "cross_eq", "attr1": "color", "value1": "yellow", "attr2": "food", "value2": "tacos"}], "solution": {"Carol": {"food": "tacos", "color": "yellow"}, "Bob": {"food": "sushi", "color": "green"}, "Grace": {"food": "pasta", "color": "purple"}}}
{"id": "51fce2df-dcf3-4d6b-ad40-1a85a385d016", "text_prompt": "There are 3 people: Alice, Quinn, Frank.\nThe attributes are: sport: football, yoga, basketball; drink: coffee, tea, juice.\nClues:\n- Quinn doesn't have coffee.\n- Quinn doesn't have basketball.\n- Alice has coffee.\n- Alice doesn't have yoga.\n- Frank doesn't have football.\n- Whoever has basketball sport has coffee drink.\n- Whoever has juice drink has football sport.\n\nDetermine which attributes correspond to each person.", "entities": ["Alice", "Quinn", "Frank"], "attributes": {"sport": ["football", "yoga", "basketball"], "drink": ["coffee", "tea", "juice"]}, "clues": [{"type": "eq", "entity": "Alice", "attr": "drink", "value": "coffee"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Quinn", "attr": "sport", "value": "basketball"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Quinn", "attr": "drink", "value": "coffee"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Frank", "attr": "sport", "value": "football"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Alice", "attr": "sport", "value": "yoga"}, {"type": "cross_eq", "attr1": "sport", "value1": "basketball", "attr2": "drink", "value2": "coffee"}, {"type": "cross_eq", "attr1": "drink", "value1": "juice", "attr2": "sport", "value2": "football"}], "solution": {"Alice": {"sport": "basketball", "drink": "coffee"}, "Quinn": {"sport": "football", "drink": "juice"}, "Frank": {"sport": "yoga", "drink": "tea"}}}
{"id": "81daf994-8e26-4357-9385-ca2f0948280f", "text_prompt": "There are 3 people: Nico, Jorge, Frank.\nThe attributes are: food: pasta, sushi, salad; sport: basketball, swimming, tennis.\nClues:\n- Jorge doesn't have tennis.\n- Whoever has swimming sport has salad food.\n- The person with salad food doesn't have basketball sport.\n- Frank doesn't have tennis.\n- Jorge has swimming.\n- Nico doesn't have sushi.\n- Frank doesn't have salad.\n\nDetermine which attributes correspond to each person.", "entities": ["Nico", "Jorge", "Frank"], "attributes": {"food": ["pasta", "sushi", "salad"], "sport": ["basketball", "swimming", "tennis"]}, "clues": [{"type": "eq", "entity": "Jorge", "attr": "sport", "value": "swimming"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Jorge", "attr": "sport", "value": "tennis"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Nico", "attr": "food", "value": "sushi"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Frank", "attr": "food", "value": "salad"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Frank", "attr": "sport", "value": "tennis"}, {"type": "cross_neq", "attr1": "food", "value1": "salad", "attr2": "sport", "value2": "basketball"}, {"type": "cross_eq", "attr1": "sport", "value1": "swimming", "attr2": "food", "value2": "salad"}], "solution": {"Nico": {"food": "pasta", "sport": "tennis"}, "Jorge": {"food": "salad", "sport": "swimming"}, "Frank": {"food": "sushi", "sport": "basketball"}}}
{"id": "0adbe948-5a87-43b8-b7cf-31cca0c4a1cd", "text_prompt": "There are 3 people: Olga, Frank, Eva.\nThe attributes are: color: blue, red, yellow; animal: hamster, dog, fish.\nClues:\n- Olga doesn't have red.\n- The person with yellow color doesn't have dog animal.\n- Frank doesn't have yellow.\n- Eva doesn't have red.\n- Olga doesn't have dog.\n- Frank has hamster.\n- The person with fish animal doesn't have blue color.\n\nDetermine which attributes correspond to each person.", "entities": ["Olga", "Frank", "Eva"], "attributes": {"color": ["blue", "red", "yellow"], "animal": ["hamster", "dog", "fish"]}, "clues": [{"type": "eq", "entity": "Frank", "attr": "animal", "value": "hamster"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Eva", "attr": "color", "value": "red"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Olga", "attr": "color", "value": "red"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Olga", "attr": "animal", "value": "dog"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Frank", "attr": "color", "value": "yellow"}, {"type": "cross_neq", "attr1": "color", "value1": "yellow", "attr2": "animal", "value2": "dog"}, {"type": "cross_neq", "attr1": "animal", "value1": "fish", "attr2": "color", "value2": "blue"}], "solution": {"Olga": {"color": "yellow", "animal": "fish"}, "Frank": {"color": "red", "animal": "hamster"}, "Eva": {"color": "blue", "animal": "dog"}}}
{"id": "2e107846-80da-418b-a0d3-688bdc2ce5c4", "text_prompt": "There are 3 people: Eva, Carol, Hugo.\nThe attributes are: color: blue, green, yellow; food: salad, sushi, pizza.\nClues:\n- Whoever has pizza food has yellow color.\n- Whoever has green color has sushi food.\n- Eva doesn't have blue.\n- Eva has yellow.\n- Eva doesn't have salad.\n- Carol doesn't have yellow.\n- Carol doesn't have green.\n\nDetermine which attributes correspond to each person.", "entities": ["Eva", "Carol", "Hugo"], "attributes": {"color": ["blue", "green", "yellow"], "food": ["salad", "sushi", "pizza"]}, "clues": [{"type": "eq", "entity": "Eva", "attr": "color", "value": "yellow"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Carol", "attr": "color", "value": "yellow"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Eva", "attr": "food", "value": "salad"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Carol", "attr": "color", "value": "green"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Eva", "attr": "color", "value": "blue"}, {"type": "cross_eq", "attr1": "food", "value1": "pizza", "attr2": "color", "value2": "yellow"}, {"type": "cross_eq", "attr1": "color", "value1": "green", "attr2": "food", "value2": "sushi"}], "solution": {"Eva": {"color": "yellow", "food": "pizza"}, "Carol": {"color": "blue", "food": "salad"}, "Hugo": {"color": "green", "food": "sushi"}}}
{"id": "c31ef2f3-0b3c-4a7c-ba22-1d91956961e4", "text_prompt": "There are 3 people: Bob, David, Frank.\nThe attributes are: color: purple, yellow, red; sport: yoga, football, basketball.\nClues:\n- Bob doesn't have basketball.\n- David doesn't have red.\n- David doesn't have purple.\n- Whoever has basketball sport has yellow color.\n- The person with red color doesn't have basketball sport.\n- Bob doesn't have red.\n- Bob has yoga.\n\nDetermine which attributes correspond to each person.", "entities": ["Bob", "David", "Frank"], "attributes": {"color": ["purple", "yellow", "red"], "sport": ["yoga", "football", "basketball"]}, "clues": [{"type": "eq", "entity": "Bob", "attr": "sport", "value": "yoga"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Bob", "attr": "sport", "value": "basketball"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Bob", "attr": "color", "value": "red"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "David", "attr": "color", "value": "red"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "David", "attr": "color", "value": "purple"}, {"type": "cross_neq", "attr1": "color", "value1": "red", "attr2": "sport", "value2": "basketball"}, {"type": "cross_eq", "attr1": "sport", "value1": "basketball", "attr2": "color", "value2": "yellow"}], "solution": {"Bob": {"color": "purple", "sport": "yoga"}, "David": {"color": "yellow", "sport": "basketball"}, "Frank": {"color": "red", "sport": "football"}}}
{"id": "b6bae0f4-9b0a-422d-beb0-9d580d0386ef", "text_prompt": "There are 3 people: Marta, Jorge, Vera.\nThe attributes are: drink: water, coffee, juice; food: sushi, salad, tacos.\nClues:\n- Vera doesn't have juice.\n- Whoever has coffee drink has salad food.\n- Jorge has sushi.\n- Vera doesn't have coffee.\n- The person with tacos food doesn't have juice drink.\n- Vera doesn't have sushi.\n- Marta doesn't have tacos.\n\nDetermine which attributes correspond to each person.", "entities": ["Marta", "Jorge", "Vera"], "attributes": {"drink": ["water", "coffee", "juice"], "food": ["sushi", "salad", "tacos"]}, "clues": [{"type": "eq", "entity": "Jorge", "attr": "food", "value": "sushi"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Vera", "attr": "drink", "value": "coffee"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Vera", "attr": "drink", "value": "juice"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Vera", "attr": "food", "value": "sushi"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Marta", "attr": "food", "value": "tacos"}, {"type": "cross_neq", "attr1": "food", "value1": "tacos", "attr2": "drink", "value2": "juice"}, {"type": "cross_eq", "attr1": "drink", "value1": "coffee", "attr2": "food", "value2": "salad"}], "solution": {"Marta": {"drink": "coffee", "food": "salad"}, "Jorge": {"drink": "juice", "food": "sushi"}, "Vera": {"drink": "water", "food": "tacos"}}}
{"id": "56c6b461-b107-4342-b7e1-e972f5429eaf", "text_prompt": "There are 3 people: Eva, Sara, Grace.\nThe attributes are: city: Paris, Berlin, Rome; color: yellow, red, purple.\nClues:\n- Whoever has Berlin city has yellow color.\n- Eva doesn't have Rome.\n- Grace doesn't have purple.\n- The person with red color doesn't have Berlin city.\n- Sara has Rome.\n- Sara doesn't have purple.\n- Grace doesn't have Paris.\n\nDetermine which attributes correspond to each person.", "entities": ["Eva", "Sara", "Grace"], "attributes": {"city": ["Paris", "Berlin", "Rome"], "color": ["yellow", "red", "purple"]}, "clues": [{"type": "eq", "entity": "Sara", "attr": "city", "value": "Rome"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Grace", "attr": "color", "value": "purple"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Eva", "attr": "city", "value": "Rome"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Sara", "attr": "color", "value": "purple"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Grace", "attr": "city", "value": "Paris"}, {"type": "cross_eq", "attr1": "city", "value1": "Berlin", "attr2": "color", "value2": "yellow"}, {"type": "cross_neq", "attr1": "color", "value1": "red", "attr2": "city", "value2": "Berlin"}], "solution": {"Eva": {"city": "Paris", "color": "purple"}, "Sara": {"city": "Rome", "color": "red"}, "Grace": {"city": "Berlin", "color": "yellow"}}}
{"id": "524093cf-5cbd-4b8d-a7ae-0ee6cf846c1c", "text_prompt": "There are 3 people: Bob, Sara, Alice.\nThe attributes are: drink: soda, juice, coffee; animal: fish, hamster, dog.\nClues:\n- Sara doesn't have dog.\n- Sara has fish.\n- Bob doesn't have soda.\n- Whoever has fish animal has coffee drink.\n- Bob doesn't have coffee.\n- Whoever has dog animal has soda drink.\n- Alice doesn't have juice.\n\nDetermine which attributes correspond to each person.", "entities": ["Bob", "Sara", "Alice"], "attributes": {"drink": ["soda", "juice", "coffee"], "animal": ["fish", "hamster", "dog"]}, "clues": [{"type": "eq", "entity": "Sara", "attr": "animal", "value": "fish"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Sara", "attr": "animal", "value": "dog"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Bob", "attr": "drink", "value": "coffee"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Alice", "attr": "drink", "value": "juice"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Bob", "attr": "drink", "value": "soda"}, {"type": "cross_eq", "attr1": "animal", "value1": "fish", "attr2": "drink", "value2": "coffee"}, {"type": "cross_eq", "attr1": "animal", "value1": "dog", "attr2": "drink", "value2": "soda"}], "solution": {"Bob": {"drink": "juice", "animal": "hamster"}, "Sara": {"drink": "coffee", "animal": "fish"}, "Alice": {"drink": "soda", "animal": "dog"}}}
{"id": "74c0456a-7e62-4ed9-b3b3-f36c64108dec", "text_prompt": "There are 3 people: Grace, David, Frank.\nThe attributes are: food: salad, tacos, pizza; sport: swimming, tennis, yoga.\nClues:\n- Grace doesn't have swimming.\n- The person with tacos food doesn't have yoga sport.\n- The person with swimming sport doesn't have tacos food.\n- Frank doesn't have pizza.\n- Frank doesn't have swimming.\n- Grace doesn't have yoga.\n- Grace has tacos.\n\nDetermine which attributes correspond to each person.", "entities": ["Grace", "David", "Frank"], "attributes": {"food": ["salad", "tacos", "pizza"], "sport": ["swimming", "tennis", "yoga"]}, "clues": [{"type": "eq", "entity": "Grace", "attr": "food", "value": "tacos"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Grace", "attr": "sport", "value": "yoga"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Grace", "attr": "sport", "value": "swimming"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Frank", "attr": "sport", "value": "swimming"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Frank", "attr": "food", "value": "pizza"}, {"type": "cross_neq", "attr1": "food", "value1": "tacos", "attr2": "sport", "value2": "yoga"}, {"type": "cross_neq", "attr1": "sport", "value1": "swimming", "attr2": "food", "value2": "tacos"}], "solution": {"Grace": {"food": "tacos", "sport": "tennis"}, "David": {"food": "pizza", "sport": "swimming"}, "Frank": {"food": "salad", "sport": "yoga"}}}
{"id": "a1459b31-5980-4a79-bfc9-2eb2a5aea5a0", "text_prompt": "There are 3 people: Quinn, Alice, Frank.\nThe attributes are: sport: swimming, basketball, football; drink: coffee, soda, water.\nClues:\n- Alice doesn't have coffee.\n- Frank doesn't have basketball.\n- Whoever has swimming sport has coffee drink.\n- Alice doesn't have water.\n- The person with water drink doesn't have swimming sport.\n- Quinn has coffee.\n- Frank doesn't have soda.\n\nDetermine which attributes correspond to each person.", "entities": ["Quinn", "Alice", "Frank"], "attributes": {"sport": ["swimming", "basketball", "football"], "drink": ["coffee", "soda", "water"]}, "clues": [{"type": "eq", "entity": "Quinn", "attr": "drink", "value": "coffee"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Alice", "attr": "drink", "value": "coffee"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Frank", "attr": "sport", "value": "basketball"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Frank", "attr": "drink", "value": "soda"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Alice", "attr": "drink", "value": "water"}, {"type": "cross_neq", "attr1": "drink", "value1": "water", "attr2": "sport", "value2": "swimming"}, {"type": "cross_eq", "attr1": "sport", "value1": "swimming", "attr2": "drink", "value2": "coffee"}], "solution": {"Quinn": {"sport": "swimming", "drink": "coffee"}, "Alice": {"sport": "basketball", "drink": "soda"}, "Frank": {"sport": "football", "drink": "water"}}}
{"id": "7b61b728-42c5-4190-9a1a-0ff725ce2187", "text_prompt": "There are 3 people: Alice, Marta, David.\nThe attributes are: food: pasta, tacos, sushi; animal: bird, hamster, cat.\nClues:\n- David has tacos.\n- Alice doesn't have sushi.\n- David doesn't have pasta.\n- The person with hamster animal doesn't have pasta food.\n- Marta doesn't have bird.\n- The person with sushi food doesn't have bird animal.\n- Alice doesn't have bird.\n\nDetermine which attributes correspond to each person.", "entities": ["Alice", "Marta", "David"], "attributes": {"food": ["pasta", "tacos", "sushi"], "animal": ["bird", "hamster", "cat"]}, "clues": [{"type": "eq", "entity": "David", "attr": "food", "value": "tacos"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Alice", "attr": "food", "value": "sushi"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "David", "attr": "food", "value": "pasta"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Marta", "attr": "animal", "value": "bird"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Alice", "attr": "animal", "value": "bird"}, {"type": "cross_neq", "attr1": "food", "value1": "sushi", "attr2": "animal", "value2": "bird"}, {"type": "cross_neq", "attr1": "animal", "value1": "hamster", "attr2": "food", "value2": "pasta"}], "solution": {"Alice": {"food": "pasta", "animal": "cat"}, "Marta": {"food": "sushi", "animal": "hamster"}, "David": {"food": "tacos", "animal": "bird"}}}
{"id": "4a4ffd65-ecd0-48e7-ac85-eefaec3955a7", "text_prompt": "There are 3 people: Bob, Marta, David.\nThe attributes are: sport: football, swimming, basketball; animal: dog, cat, hamster.\nClues:\n- Marta has swimming.\n- Whoever has basketball sport has hamster animal.\n- David doesn't have cat.\n- Marta doesn't have football.\n- Bob doesn't have cat.\n- David doesn't have hamster.\n- Whoever has hamster animal has basketball sport.\n\nDetermine which attributes correspond to each person.", "entities": ["Bob", "Marta", "David"], "attributes": {"sport": ["football", "swimming", "basketball"], "animal": ["dog", "cat", "hamster"]}, "clues": [{"type": "eq", "entity": "Marta", "attr": "sport", "value": "swimming"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Marta", "attr": "sport", "value": "football"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "David", "attr": "animal", "value": "hamster"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Bob", "attr": "animal", "value": "cat"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "David", "attr": "animal", "value": "cat"}, {"type": "cross_eq", "attr1": "sport", "value1": "basketball", "attr2": "animal", "value2": "hamster"}, {"type": "cross_eq", "attr1": "animal", "value1": "hamster", "attr2": "sport", "value2": "basketball"}], "solution": {"Bob": {"sport": "basketball", "animal": "hamster"}, "Marta": {"sport": "swimming", "animal": "cat"}, "David": {"sport": "football", "animal": "dog"}}}
{"id": "9e86568e-c3d1-4d17-b1ea-9c1dfb3fe1d4", "text_prompt": "There are 3 people: Olga, Vera, Jorge.\nThe attributes are: sport: basketball, swimming, football; drink: water, tea, soda.\nClues:\n- Vera doesn't have soda.\n- Whoever has soda drink has football sport.\n- Jorge doesn't have water.\n- Olga doesn't have water.\n- Vera doesn't have basketball.\n- Jorge has football.\n- The person with basketball sport doesn't have water drink.\n\nDetermine which attributes correspond to each person.", "entities": ["Olga", "Vera", "Jorge"], "attributes": {"sport": ["basketball", "swimming", "football"], "drink": ["water", "tea", "soda"]}, "clues": [{"type": "eq", "entity": "Jorge", "attr": "sport", "value": "football"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Olga", "attr": "drink", "value": "water"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Vera", "attr": "drink", "value": "soda"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Jorge", "attr": "drink", "value": "water"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Vera", "attr": "sport", "value": "basketball"}, {"type": "cross_neq", "attr1": "sport", "value1": "basketball", "attr2": "drink", "value2": "water"}, {"type": "cross_eq", "attr1": "drink", "value1": "soda", "attr2": "sport", "value2": "football"}], "solution": {"Olga": {"sport": "basketball", "drink": "tea"}, "Vera": {"sport": "swimming", "drink": "water"}, "Jorge": {"sport": "football", "drink": "soda"}}}
{"id": "9418b463-4708-40fc-b5b6-31ff8c4c2ff6", "text_prompt": "There are 3 people: Hugo, Eva, Vera.\nThe attributes are: animal: fish, dog, bird; drink: juice, coffee, soda.\nClues:\n- Whoever has dog animal has juice drink.\n- Vera doesn't have bird.\n- Eva doesn't have soda.\n- The person with coffee drink doesn't have fish animal.\n- Eva doesn't have juice.\n- Hugo doesn't have juice.\n- Eva has bird.\n\nDetermine which attributes correspond to each person.", "entities": ["Hugo", "Eva", "Vera"], "attributes": {"animal": ["fish", "dog", "bird"], "drink": ["juice", "coffee", "soda"]}, "clues": [{"type": "eq", "entity": "Eva", "attr": "animal", "value": "bird"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Eva", "attr": "drink", "value": "juice"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Vera", "attr": "animal", "value": "bird"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Hugo", "attr": "drink", "value": "juice"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Eva", "attr": "drink", "value": "soda"}, {"type": "cross_neq", "attr1": "drink", "value1": "coffee", "attr2": "animal", "value2": "fish"}, {"type": "cross_eq", "attr1": "animal", "value1": "dog", "attr2": "drink", "value2": "juice"}], "solution": {"Hugo": {"animal": "fish", "drink": "soda"}, "Eva": {"animal": "bird", "drink": "coffee"}, "Vera": {"animal": "dog", "drink": "juice"}}}
{"id": "a1a36bb2-3000-4233-a502-7269ba2c416b", "text_prompt": "There are 3 people: Nico, Bob, Marta.\nThe attributes are: sport: basketball, yoga, tennis; animal: dog, bird, fish.\nClues:\n- Nico doesn't have fish.\n- Whoever has fish animal has tennis sport.\n- Marta doesn't have basketball.\n- The person with tennis sport doesn't have dog animal.\n- Nico doesn't have tennis.\n- Nico doesn't have yoga.\n- Bob has dog.\n\nDetermine which attributes correspond to each person.", "entities": ["Nico", "Bob", "Marta"], "attributes": {"sport": ["basketball", "yoga", "tennis"], "animal": ["dog", "bird", "fish"]}, "clues": [{"type": "eq", "entity": "Bob", "attr": "animal", "value": "dog"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Nico", "attr": "sport", "value": "yoga"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Marta", "attr": "sport", "value": "basketball"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Nico", "attr": "animal", "value": "fish"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Nico", "attr": "sport", "value": "tennis"}, {"type": "cross_eq", "attr1": "animal", "value1": "fish", "attr2": "sport", "value2": "tennis"}, {"type": "cross_neq", "attr1": "sport", "value1": "tennis", "attr2": "animal", "value2": "dog"}], "solution": {"Nico": {"sport": "basketball", "animal": "bird"}, "Bob": {"sport": "yoga", "animal": "dog"}, "Marta": {"sport": "tennis", "animal": "fish"}}}
{"id": "3d2e8cc1-46db-4fab-9985-e7980c3efb05", "text_prompt": "There are 3 people: Irene, Frank, Marta.\nThe attributes are: color: yellow, purple, green; drink: juice, coffee, soda.\nClues:\n- Frank doesn't have purple.\n- Marta doesn't have juice.\n- Whoever has soda drink has yellow color.\n- Marta doesn't have purple.\n- Whoever has purple color has juice drink.\n- Marta has green.\n- Frank doesn't have coffee.\n\nDetermine which attributes correspond to each person.", "entities": ["Irene", "Frank", "Marta"], "attributes": {"color": ["yellow", "purple", "green"], "drink": ["juice", "coffee", "soda"]}, "clues": [{"type": "eq", "entity": "Marta", "attr": "color", "value": "green"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Frank", "attr": "color", "value": "purple"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Marta", "attr": "color", "value": "purple"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Marta", "attr": "drink", "value": "juice"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Frank", "attr": "drink", "value": "coffee"}, {"type": "cross_eq", "attr1": "color", "value1": "purple", "attr2": "drink", "value2": "juice"}, {"type": "cross_eq", "attr1": "drink", "value1": "soda", "attr2": "color", "value2": "yellow"}], "solution": {"Irene": {"color": "purple", "drink": "juice"}, "Frank": {"color": "yellow", "drink": "soda"}, "Marta": {"color": "green", "drink": "coffee"}}}
{"id": "31329c81-386e-45a7-a7c7-48f70ac66ef5", "text_prompt": "There are 3 people: Marta, Grace, Nico.\nThe attributes are: food: pasta, tacos, salad; color: red, yellow, purple.\nClues:\n- Nico doesn't have red.\n- The person with red color doesn't have tacos food.\n- Grace has purple.\n- Nico doesn't have tacos.\n- Marta doesn't have pasta.\n- The person with tacos food doesn't have red color.\n- Nico doesn't have purple.\n\nDetermine which attributes correspond to each person.", "entities": ["Marta", "Grace", "Nico"], "attributes": {"food": ["pasta", "tacos", "salad"], "color": ["red", "yellow", "purple"]}, "clues": [{"type": "eq", "entity": "Grace", "attr": "color", "value": "purple"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Nico", "attr": "food", "value": "tacos"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Nico", "attr": "color", "value": "red"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Nico", "attr": "color", "value": "purple"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Marta", "attr": "food", "value": "pasta"}, {"type": "cross_neq", "attr1": "color", "value1": "red", "attr2": "food", "value2": "tacos"}, {"type": "cross_neq", "attr1": "food", "value1": "tacos", "attr2": "color", "value2": "red"}], "solution": {"Marta": {"food": "salad", "color": "red"}, "Grace": {"food": "tacos", "color": "purple"}, "Nico": {"food": "pasta", "color": "yellow"}}}
{"id": "930227a2-cf60-48de-be83-fa3696dbfadc", "text_prompt": "There are 3 people: David, Carol, Alice.\nThe attributes are: sport: tennis, swimming, yoga; drink: juice, soda, coffee.\nClues:\n- Carol has soda.\n- Alice doesn't have soda.\n- Whoever has juice drink has yoga sport.\n- Alice doesn't have juice.\n- David doesn't have tennis.\n- Whoever has swimming sport has coffee drink.\n- David doesn't have coffee.\n\nDetermine which attributes correspond to each person.", "entities": ["David", "Carol", "Alice"], "attributes": {"sport": ["tennis", "swimming", "yoga"], "drink": ["juice", "soda", "coffee"]}, "clues": [{"type": "eq", "entity": "Carol", "attr": "drink", "value": "soda"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "David", "attr": "sport", "value": "tennis"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Alice", "attr": "drink", "value": "soda"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "David", "attr": "drink", "value": "coffee"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Alice", "attr": "drink", "value": "juice"}, {"type": "cross_eq", "attr1": "drink", "value1": "juice", "attr2": "sport", "value2": "yoga"}, {"type": "cross_eq", "attr1": "sport", "value1": "swimming", "attr2": "drink", "value2": "coffee"}], "solution": {"David": {"sport": "yoga", "drink": "juice"}, "Carol": {"sport": "tennis", "drink": "soda"}, "Alice": {"sport": "swimming", "drink": "coffee"}}}
{"id": "6f6c5221-3e21-4f9d-9539-e682bb9f3a2d", "text_prompt": "There are 3 people: Sara, Nico, Irene.\nThe attributes are: drink: juice, coffee, tea; animal: fish, bird, cat.\nClues:\n- Irene has tea.\n- Irene doesn't have juice.\n- Sara doesn't have bird.\n- Irene doesn't have cat.\n- The person with fish animal doesn't have juice drink.\n- Sara doesn't have tea.\n- Whoever has juice drink has bird animal.\n\nDetermine which attributes correspond to each person.", "entities": ["Sara", "Nico", "Irene"], "attributes": {"drink": ["juice", "coffee", "tea"], "animal": ["fish", "bird", "cat"]}, "clues": [{"type": "eq", "entity": "Irene", "attr": "drink", "value": "tea"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Sara", "attr": "drink", "value": "tea"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Irene", "attr": "drink", "value": "juice"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Irene", "attr": "animal", "value": "cat"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Sara", "attr": "animal", "value": "bird"}, {"type": "cross_neq", "attr1": "animal", "value1": "fish", "attr2": "drink", "value2": "juice"}, {"type": "cross_eq", "attr1": "drink", "value1": "juice", "attr2": "animal", "value2": "bird"}], "solution": {"Sara": {"drink": "coffee", "animal": "cat"}, "Nico": {"drink": "juice", "animal": "bird"}, "Irene": {"drink": "tea", "animal": "fish"}}}
{"id": "fa6d3478-55c4-48ad-8163-4a0b22ae5de3", "text_prompt": "There are 3 people: Olga, Alice, Pablo.\nThe attributes are: animal: hamster, bird, fish; city: Madrid, Berlin, Rome.\nClues:\n- Whoever has Berlin city has hamster animal.\n- Alice has hamster.\n- Alice doesn't have fish.\n- Whoever has hamster animal has Berlin city.\n- Olga doesn't have fish.\n- Pablo doesn't have Madrid.\n- Pablo doesn't have bird.\n\nDetermine which attributes correspond to each person.", "entities": ["Olga", "Alice", "Pablo"], "attributes": {"animal": ["hamster", "bird", "fish"], "city": ["Madrid", "Berlin", "Rome"]}, "clues": [{"type": "eq", "entity": "Alice", "attr": "animal", "value": "hamster"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Olga", "attr": "animal", "value": "fish"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Pablo", "attr": "animal", "value": "bird"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Alice", "attr": "animal", "value": "fish"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Pablo", "attr": "city", "value": "Madrid"}, {"type": "cross_eq", "attr1": "animal", "value1": "hamster", "attr2": "city", "value2": "Berlin"}, {"type": "cross_eq", "attr1": "city", "value1": "Berlin", "attr2": "animal", "value2": "hamster"}], "solution": {"Olga": {"animal": "bird", "city": "Madrid"}, "Alice": {"animal": "hamster", "city": "Berlin"}, "Pablo": {"animal": "fish", "city": "Rome"}}}
{"id": "d526effa-0676-43d8-8447-5253ae079a29", "text_prompt": "There are 3 people: Hugo, Eva, Jorge.\nThe attributes are: animal: dog, hamster, bird; city: London, Rome, Berlin.\nClues:\n- The person with Berlin city doesn't have bird animal.\n- Eva doesn't have London.\n- Jorge has Berlin.\n- Hugo doesn't have dog.\n- The person with Berlin city doesn't have hamster animal.\n- Jorge doesn't have hamster.\n- Eva doesn't have hamster.\n\nDetermine which attributes correspond to each person.", "entities": ["Hugo", "Eva", "Jorge"], "attributes": {"animal": ["dog", "hamster", "bird"], "city": ["London", "Rome", "Berlin"]}, "clues": [{"type": "eq", "entity": "Jorge", "attr": "city", "value": "Berlin"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Eva", "attr": "animal", "value": "hamster"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Hugo", "attr": "animal", "value": "dog"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Eva", "attr": "city", "value": "London"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Jorge", "attr": "animal", "value": "hamster"}, {"type": "cross_neq", "attr1": "city", "value1": "Berlin", "attr2": "animal", "value2": "hamster"}, {"type": "cross_neq", "attr1": "city", "value1": "Berlin", "attr2": "animal", "value2": "bird"}], "solution": {"Hugo": {"animal": "hamster", "city": "London"}, "Eva": {"animal": "bird", "city": "Rome"}, "Jorge": {"animal": "dog", "city": "Berlin"}}}
{"id": "50413dd2-d45d-4b03-bc7f-c84e342c0241", "text_prompt": "There are 3 people: Frank, Bob, Alice.\nThe attributes are: animal: cat, hamster, dog; drink: water, soda, tea.\nClues:\n- Bob doesn't have tea.\n- The person with cat animal doesn't have water drink.\n- Bob doesn't have cat.\n- Frank has dog.\n- Frank doesn't have soda.\n- The person with cat animal doesn't have tea drink.\n- Bob doesn't have soda.\n\nDetermine which attributes correspond to each person.", "entities": ["Frank", "Bob", "Alice"], "attributes": {"animal": ["cat", "hamster", "dog"], "drink": ["water", "soda", "tea"]}, "clues": [{"type": "eq", "entity": "Frank", "attr": "animal", "value": "dog"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Bob", "attr": "animal", "value": "cat"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Bob", "attr": "drink", "value": "tea"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Bob", "attr": "drink", "value": "soda"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Frank", "attr": "drink", "value": "soda"}, {"type": "cross_neq", "attr1": "animal", "value1": "cat", "attr2": "drink", "value2": "tea"}, {"type": "cross_neq", "attr1": "animal", "value1": "cat", "attr2": "drink", "value2": "water"}], "solution": {"Frank": {"animal": "dog", "drink": "tea"}, "Bob": {"animal": "hamster", "drink": "water"}, "Alice": {"animal": "cat", "drink": "soda"}}}
{"id": "ba86cfb8-c5df-4bf2-b6e2-3831ba4b862c", "text_prompt": "There are 3 people: Grace, Eva, Alice.\nThe attributes are: food: sushi, pasta, tacos; city: Rome, London, Berlin.\nClues:\n- Eva doesn't have tacos.\n- Alice doesn't have tacos.\n- Grace doesn't have pasta.\n- Alice has Rome.\n- Whoever has pasta food has London city.\n- Alice doesn't have Berlin.\n- Whoever has London city has pasta food.\n\nDetermine which attributes correspond to each person.", "entities": ["Grace", "Eva", "Alice"], "attributes": {"food": ["sushi", "pasta", "tacos"], "city": ["Rome", "London", "Berlin"]}, "clues": [{"type": "eq", "entity": "Alice", "attr": "city", "value": "Rome"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Alice", "attr": "city", "value": "Berlin"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Eva", "attr": "food", "value": "tacos"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Alice", "attr": "food", "value": "tacos"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Grace", "attr": "food", "value": "pasta"}, {"type": "cross_eq", "attr1": "food", "value1": "pasta", "attr2": "city", "value2": "London"}, {"type": "cross_eq", "attr1": "city", "value1": "London", "attr2": "food", "value2": "pasta"}], "solution": {"Grace": {"food": "tacos", "city": "Berlin"}, "Eva": {"food": "pasta", "city": "London"}, "Alice": {"food": "sushi", "city": "Rome"}}}
{"id": "8ee9f342-85a7-4757-8d24-c06fc79dca55", "text_prompt": "There are 3 people: Nico, Grace, Alice.\nThe attributes are: sport: football, basketball, swimming; drink: tea, soda, water.\nClues:\n- Whoever has water drink has basketball sport.\n- The person with swimming sport doesn't have soda drink.\n- Grace doesn't have football.\n- Alice has football.\n- Grace doesn't have soda.\n- Nico doesn't have water.\n- Alice doesn't have tea.\n\nDetermine which attributes correspond to each person.", "entities": ["Nico", "Grace", "Alice"], "attributes": {"sport": ["football", "basketball", "swimming"], "drink": ["tea", "soda", "water"]}, "clues": [{"type": "eq", "entity": "Alice", "attr": "sport", "value": "football"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Alice", "attr": "drink", "value": "tea"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Grace", "attr": "sport", "value": "football"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Grace", "attr": "drink", "value": "soda"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Nico", "attr": "drink", "value": "water"}, {"type": "cross_neq", "attr1": "sport", "value1": "swimming", "attr2": "drink", "value2": "soda"}, {"type": "cross_eq", "attr1": "drink", "value1": "water", "attr2": "sport", "value2": "basketball"}], "solution": {"Nico": {"sport": "swimming", "drink": "tea"}, "Grace": {"sport": "basketball", "drink": "water"}, "Alice": {"sport": "football", "drink": "soda"}}}
{"id": "4f31c6db-2c00-4174-bb73-39c8306a5b7b", "text_prompt": "There are 3 people: Grace, Alice, Hugo.\nThe attributes are: animal: cat, dog, bird; drink: soda, tea, water.\nClues:\n- Alice has water.\n- Alice doesn't have bird.\n- Whoever has cat animal has soda drink.\n- The person with water drink doesn't have bird animal.\n- Hugo doesn't have tea.\n- Alice doesn't have tea.\n- Hugo doesn't have dog.\n\nDetermine which attributes correspond to each person.", "entities": ["Grace", "Alice", "Hugo"], "attributes": {"animal": ["cat", "dog", "bird"], "drink": ["soda", "tea", "water"]}, "clues": [{"type": "eq", "entity": "Alice", "attr": "drink", "value": "water"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Alice", "attr": "animal", "value": "bird"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Hugo", "attr": "animal", "value": "dog"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Alice", "attr": "drink", "value": "tea"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Hugo", "attr": "drink", "value": "tea"}, {"type": "cross_neq", "attr1": "drink", "value1": "water", "attr2": "animal", "value2": "bird"}, {"type": "cross_eq", "attr1": "animal", "value1": "cat", "attr2": "drink", "value2": "soda"}], "solution": {"Grace": {"animal": "bird", "drink": "tea"}, "Alice": {"animal": "dog", "drink": "water"}, "Hugo": {"animal": "cat", "drink": "soda"}}}
{"id": "f1b90ebe-de48-4cc6-a71f-8dcfb7391d43", "text_prompt": "There are 3 people: Vera, Eva, Frank.\nThe attributes are: animal: hamster, fish, bird; color: blue, red, yellow.\nClues:\n- Vera doesn't have hamster.\n- Vera doesn't have red.\n- Whoever has fish animal has yellow color.\n- Vera doesn't have fish.\n- Eva doesn't have fish.\n- Frank has yellow.\n- The person with blue color doesn't have hamster animal.\n\nDetermine which attributes correspond to each person.", "entities": ["Vera", "Eva", "Frank"], "attributes": {"animal": ["hamster", "fish", "bird"], "color": ["blue", "red", "yellow"]}, "clues": [{"type": "eq", "entity": "Frank", "attr": "color", "value": "yellow"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Vera", "attr": "animal", "value": "fish"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Eva", "attr": "animal", "value": "fish"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Vera", "attr": "animal", "value": "hamster"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Vera", "attr": "color", "value": "red"}, {"type": "cross_neq", "attr1": "color", "value1": "blue", "attr2": "animal", "value2": "hamster"}, {"type": "cross_eq", "attr1": "animal", "value1": "fish", "attr2": "color", "value2": "yellow"}], "solution": {"Vera": {"animal": "bird", "color": "blue"}, "Eva": {"animal": "hamster", "color": "red"}, "Frank": {"animal": "fish", "color": "yellow"}}}
{"id": "edd1e838-2454-48cd-baf8-de277ea965ec", "text_prompt": "There are 3 people: Eva, Irene, David.\nThe attributes are: food: sushi, tacos, pasta; drink: juice, tea, soda.\nClues:\n- Eva has tacos.\n- Eva doesn't have juice.\n- Eva doesn't have tea.\n- David doesn't have pasta.\n- David doesn't have tacos.\n- The person with tacos food doesn't have tea drink.\n- Whoever has tea drink has sushi food.\n\nDetermine which attributes correspond to each person.", "entities": ["Eva", "Irene", "David"], "attributes": {"food": ["sushi", "tacos", "pasta"], "drink": ["juice", "tea", "soda"]}, "clues": [{"type": "eq", "entity": "Eva", "attr": "food", "value": "tacos"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "David", "attr": "food", "value": "pasta"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Eva", "attr": "drink", "value": "tea"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "David", "attr": "food", "value": "tacos"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Eva", "attr": "drink", "value": "juice"}, {"type": "cross_neq", "attr1": "food", "value1": "tacos", "attr2": "drink", "value2": "tea"}, {"type": "cross_eq", "attr1": "drink", "value1": "tea", "attr2": "food", "value2": "sushi"}], "solution": {"Eva": {"food": "tacos", "drink": "soda"}, "Irene": {"food": "pasta", "drink": "juice"}, "David": {"food": "sushi", "drink": "tea"}}}
{"id": "8bc8c419-33bb-4234-9af6-86ec3cfc0fbe", "text_prompt": "There are 3 people: Pablo, Hugo, Jorge.\nThe attributes are: drink: water, coffee, juice; city: Rome, Berlin, London.\nClues:\n- Pablo doesn't have London.\n- Whoever has London city has coffee drink.\n- Pablo has juice.\n- The person with coffee drink doesn't have Rome city.\n- Hugo doesn't have Berlin.\n- Hugo doesn't have Rome.\n- Pablo doesn't have Rome.\n\nDetermine which attributes correspond to each person.", "entities": ["Pablo", "Hugo", "Jorge"], "attributes": {"drink": ["water", "coffee", "juice"], "city": ["Rome", "Berlin", "London"]}, "clues": [{"type": "eq", "entity": "Pablo", "attr": "drink", "value": "juice"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Hugo", "attr": "city", "value": "Berlin"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Pablo", "attr": "city", "value": "London"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Pablo", "attr": "city", "value": "Rome"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Hugo", "attr": "city", "value": "Rome"}, {"type": "cross_neq", "attr1": "drink", "value1": "coffee", "attr2": "city", "value2": "Rome"}, {"type": "cross_eq", "attr1": "city", "value1": "London", "attr2": "drink", "value2": "coffee"}], "solution": {"Pablo": {"drink": "juice", "city": "Berlin"}, "Hugo": {"drink": "coffee", "city": "London"}, "Jorge": {"drink": "water", "city": "Rome"}}}
{"id": "af69e6eb-08bb-4b9b-9791-2b38916c4fe4", "text_prompt": "There are 3 people: Grace, Marta, Frank.\nThe attributes are: city: Paris, London, Berlin; drink: coffee, soda, water.\nClues:\n- Frank doesn't have Berlin.\n- The person with Paris city doesn't have water drink.\n- Marta doesn't have Paris.\n- Marta has soda.\n- Grace doesn't have soda.\n- Frank doesn't have Paris.\n- The person with coffee drink doesn't have Berlin city.\n\nDetermine which attributes correspond to each person.", "entities": ["Grace", "Marta", "Frank"], "attributes": {"city": ["Paris", "London", "Berlin"], "drink": ["coffee", "soda", "water"]}, "clues": [{"type": "eq", "entity": "Marta", "attr": "drink", "value": "soda"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Marta", "attr": "city", "value": "Paris"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Frank", "attr": "city", "value": "Berlin"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Frank", "attr": "city", "value": "Paris"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Grace", "attr": "drink", "value": "soda"}, {"type": "cross_neq", "attr1": "drink", "value1": "coffee", "attr2": "city", "value2": "Berlin"}, {"type": "cross_neq", "attr1": "city", "value1": "Paris", "attr2": "drink", "value2": "water"}], "solution": {"Grace": {"city": "Paris", "drink": "coffee"}, "Marta": {"city": "Berlin", "drink": "soda"}, "Frank": {"city": "London", "drink": "water"}}}
{"id": "4753e242-b027-4ea4-80a1-f01da2261d6d", "text_prompt": "There are 3 people: David, Sara, Alice.\nThe attributes are: drink: water, coffee, juice; animal: bird, hamster, cat.\nClues:\n- The person with water drink doesn't have bird animal.\n- Sara doesn't have coffee.\n- David doesn't have water.\n- Sara has hamster.\n- Alice doesn't have water.\n- Alice doesn't have coffee.\n- The person with bird animal doesn't have coffee drink.\n\nDetermine which attributes correspond to each person.", "entities": ["David", "Sara", "Alice"], "attributes": {"drink": ["water", "coffee", "juice"], "animal": ["bird", "hamster", "cat"]}, "clues": [{"type": "eq", "entity": "Sara", "attr": "animal", "value": "hamster"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Sara", "attr": "drink", "value": "coffee"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "David", "attr": "drink", "value": "water"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Alice", "attr": "drink", "value": "coffee"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Alice", "attr": "drink", "value": "water"}, {"type": "cross_neq", "attr1": "drink", "value1": "water", "attr2": "animal", "value2": "bird"}, {"type": "cross_neq", "attr1": "animal", "value1": "bird", "attr2": "drink", "value2": "coffee"}], "solution": {"David": {"drink": "coffee", "animal": "cat"}, "Sara": {"drink": "water", "animal": "hamster"}, "Alice": {"drink": "juice", "animal": "bird"}}}
{"id": "ec0fa34c-5844-43c6-b4da-a2098638baba", "text_prompt": "There are 3 people: Jorge, David, Alice.\nThe attributes are: color: blue, red, yellow; sport: yoga, football, tennis.\nClues:\n- Alice doesn't have yellow.\n- David doesn't have yellow.\n- Alice doesn't have football.\n- Whoever has football sport has yellow color.\n- David has tennis.\n- Whoever has red color has tennis sport.\n- Jorge doesn't have red.\n\nDetermine which attributes correspond to each person.", "entities": ["Jorge", "David", "Alice"], "attributes": {"color": ["blue", "red", "yellow"], "sport": ["yoga", "football", "tennis"]}, "clues": [{"type": "eq", "entity": "David", "attr": "sport", "value": "tennis"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Alice", "attr": "sport", "value": "football"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "David", "attr": "color", "value": "yellow"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Alice", "attr": "color", "value": "yellow"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Jorge", "attr": "color", "value": "red"}, {"type": "cross_eq", "attr1": "sport", "value1": "football", "attr2": "color", "value2": "yellow"}, {"type": "cross_eq", "attr1": "color", "value1": "red", "attr2": "sport", "value2": "tennis"}], "solution": {"Jorge": {"color": "yellow", "sport": "football"}, "David": {"color": "red", "sport": "tennis"}, "Alice": {"color": "blue", "sport": "yoga"}}}
{"id": "09913f8f-c799-4b0b-a738-105052d3adae", "text_prompt": "There are 3 people: David, Carol, Pablo.\nThe attributes are: sport: tennis, yoga, swimming; drink: tea, juice, soda.\nClues:\n- David doesn't have soda.\n- Carol doesn't have yoga.\n- David has yoga.\n- Pablo doesn't have swimming.\n- Whoever has tea drink has tennis sport.\n- Whoever has tennis sport has tea drink.\n- Carol doesn't have juice.\n\nDetermine which attributes correspond to each person.", "entities": ["David", "Carol", "Pablo"], "attributes": {"sport": ["tennis", "yoga", "swimming"], "drink": ["tea", "juice", "soda"]}, "clues": [{"type": "eq", "entity": "David", "attr": "sport", "value": "yoga"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Carol", "attr": "sport", "value": "yoga"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "David", "attr": "drink", "value": "soda"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Carol", "attr": "drink", "value": "juice"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Pablo", "attr": "sport", "value": "swimming"}, {"type": "cross_eq", "attr1": "sport", "value1": "tennis", "attr2": "drink", "value2": "tea"}, {"type": "cross_eq", "attr1": "drink", "value1": "tea", "attr2": "sport", "value2": "tennis"}], "solution": {"David": {"sport": "yoga", "drink": "juice"}, "Carol": {"sport": "swimming", "drink": "soda"}, "Pablo": {"sport": "tennis", "drink": "tea"}}}
{"id": "e4a298c0-57af-4337-991f-4abd48a83db3", "text_prompt": "There are 3 people: Marta, Olga, Frank.\nThe attributes are: sport: swimming, yoga, tennis; city: Paris, Berlin, Madrid.\nClues:\n- Olga doesn't have tennis.\n- The person with Berlin city doesn't have tennis sport.\n- Olga has yoga.\n- Marta doesn't have Berlin.\n- Marta doesn't have Madrid.\n- Whoever has tennis sport has Madrid city.\n- Frank doesn't have yoga.\n\nDetermine which attributes correspond to each person.", "entities": ["Marta", "Olga", "Frank"], "attributes": {"sport": ["swimming", "yoga", "tennis"], "city": ["Paris", "Berlin", "Madrid"]}, "clues": [{"type": "eq", "entity": "Olga", "attr": "sport", "value": "yoga"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Marta", "attr": "city", "value": "Berlin"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Frank", "attr": "sport", "value": "yoga"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Marta", "attr": "city", "value": "Madrid"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Olga", "attr": "sport", "value": "tennis"}, {"type": "cross_neq", "attr1": "city", "value1": "Berlin", "attr2": "sport", "value2": "tennis"}, {"type": "cross_eq", "attr1": "sport", "value1": "tennis", "attr2": "city", "value2": "Madrid"}], "solution": {"Marta": {"sport": "swimming", "city": "Paris"}, "Olga": {"sport": "yoga", "city": "Berlin"}, "Frank": {"sport": "tennis", "city": "Madrid"}}}
{"id": "c7cd16e4-1597-42b8-b5bc-9b1c6b81d087", "text_prompt": "There are 3 people: Pablo, Eva, Sara.\nThe attributes are: sport: tennis, football, basketball; food: pasta, salad, pizza.\nClues:\n- Eva has football.\n- Sara doesn't have pizza.\n- The person with basketball sport doesn't have salad food.\n- Pablo doesn't have salad.\n- Pablo doesn't have tennis.\n- Whoever has pizza food has basketball sport.\n- Eva doesn't have salad.\n\nDetermine which attributes correspond to each person.", "entities": ["Pablo", "Eva", "Sara"], "attributes": {"sport": ["tennis", "football", "basketball"], "food": ["pasta", "salad", "pizza"]}, "clues": [{"type": "eq", "entity": "Eva", "attr": "sport", "value": "football"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Sara", "attr": "food", "value": "pizza"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Pablo", "attr": "sport", "value": "tennis"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Pablo", "attr": "food", "value": "salad"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Eva", "attr": "food", "value": "salad"}, {"type": "cross_neq", "attr1": "sport", "value1": "basketball", "attr2": "food", "value2": "salad"}, {"type": "cross_eq", "attr1": "food", "value1": "pizza", "attr2": "sport", "value2": "basketball"}], "solution": {"Pablo": {"sport": "basketball", "food": "pizza"}, "Eva": {"sport": "football", "food": "pasta"}, "Sara": {"sport": "tennis", "food": "salad"}}}
{"id": "ee7a4e2d-2951-47c1-ac1d-a13bd0411d63", "text_prompt": "There are 3 people: Jorge, Marta, Carol.\nThe attributes are: city: Berlin, London, Paris; color: yellow, green, red.\nClues:\n- Carol has London.\n- Carol doesn't have Berlin.\n- Marta doesn't have Paris.\n- Whoever has yellow color has London city.\n- Jorge doesn't have red.\n- Jorge doesn't have Berlin.\n- Whoever has London city has yellow color.\n\nDetermine which attributes correspond to each person.", "entities": ["Jorge", "Marta", "Carol"], "attributes": {"city": ["Berlin", "London", "Paris"], "color": ["yellow", "green", "red"]}, "clues": [{"type": "eq", "entity": "Carol", "attr": "city", "value": "London"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Jorge", "attr": "city", "value": "Berlin"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Carol", "attr": "city", "value": "Berlin"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Marta", "attr": "city", "value": "Paris"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Jorge", "attr": "color", "value": "red"}, {"type": "cross_eq", "attr1": "color", "value1": "yellow", "attr2": "city", "value2": "London"}, {"type": "cross_eq", "attr1": "city", "value1": "London", "attr2": "color", "value2": "yellow"}], "solution": {"Jorge": {"city": "Paris", "color": "green"}, "Marta": {"city": "Berlin", "color": "red"}, "Carol": {"city": "London", "color": "yellow"}}}
{"id": "f8b6a17f-a20c-457d-bdd4-1fa6844ab2d5", "text_prompt": "There are 3 people: Marta, Sara, Alice.\nThe attributes are: color: blue, purple, green; sport: yoga, football, swimming.\nClues:\n- Marta doesn't have football.\n- Marta doesn't have purple.\n- Marta doesn't have green.\n- Sara doesn't have blue.\n- Alice has green.\n- Whoever has purple color has yoga sport.\n- Whoever has yoga sport has purple color.\n\nDetermine which attributes correspond to each person.", "entities": ["Marta", "Sara", "Alice"], "attributes": {"color": ["blue", "purple", "green"], "sport": ["yoga", "football", "swimming"]}, "clues": [{"type": "eq", "entity": "Alice", "attr": "color", "value": "green"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Marta", "attr": "color", "value": "purple"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Sara", "attr": "color", "value": "blue"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Marta", "attr": "color", "value": "green"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Marta", "attr": "sport", "value": "football"}, {"type": "cross_eq", "attr1": "sport", "value1": "yoga", "attr2": "color", "value2": "purple"}, {"type": "cross_eq", "attr1": "color", "value1": "purple", "attr2": "sport", "value2": "yoga"}], "solution": {"Marta": {"color": "blue", "sport": "swimming"}, "Sara": {"color": "purple", "sport": "yoga"}, "Alice": {"color": "green", "sport": "football"}}}
{"id": "c1934406-0927-4263-8a94-3f04c050f94d", "text_prompt": "There are 3 people: Grace, Vera, Alice.\nThe attributes are: sport: football, tennis, basketball; food: sushi, pasta, pizza.\nClues:\n- Whoever has football sport has sushi food.\n- Vera doesn't have basketball.\n- Whoever has sushi food has football sport.\n- Grace doesn't have pizza.\n- Vera doesn't have pasta.\n- Grace has basketball.\n- Alice doesn't have pizza.\n\nDetermine which attributes correspond to each person.", "entities": ["Grace", "Vera", "Alice"], "attributes": {"sport": ["football", "tennis", "basketball"], "food": ["sushi", "pasta", "pizza"]}, "clues": [{"type": "eq", "entity": "Grace", "attr": "sport", "value": "basketball"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Vera", "attr": "food", "value": "pasta"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Vera", "attr": "sport", "value": "basketball"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Alice", "attr": "food", "value": "pizza"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Grace", "attr": "food", "value": "pizza"}, {"type": "cross_eq", "attr1": "sport", "value1": "football", "attr2": "food", "value2": "sushi"}, {"type": "cross_eq", "attr1": "food", "value1": "sushi", "attr2": "sport", "value2": "football"}], "solution": {"Grace": {"sport": "basketball", "food": "pasta"}, "Vera": {"sport": "tennis", "food": "pizza"}, "Alice": {"sport": "football", "food": "sushi"}}}
{"id": "119e5a61-6b65-454e-9817-ba1f55e36f82", "text_prompt": "There are 3 people: David, Jorge, Hugo.\nThe attributes are: sport: football, basketball, yoga; food: tacos, sushi, salad.\nClues:\n- Jorge has football.\n- Whoever has football sport has sushi food.\n- Jorge doesn't have yoga.\n- Hugo doesn't have tacos.\n- David doesn't have basketball.\n- The person with salad food doesn't have football sport.\n- Jorge doesn't have tacos.\n\nDetermine which attributes correspond to each person.", "entities": ["David", "Jorge", "Hugo"], "attributes": {"sport": ["football", "basketball", "yoga"], "food": ["tacos", "sushi", "salad"]}, "clues": [{"type": "eq", "entity": "Jorge", "attr": "sport", "value": "football"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Jorge", "attr": "sport", "value": "yoga"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "David", "attr": "sport", "value": "basketball"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Jorge", "attr": "food", "value": "tacos"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Hugo", "attr": "food", "value": "tacos"}, {"type": "cross_eq", "attr1": "sport", "value1": "football", "attr2": "food", "value2": "sushi"}, {"type": "cross_neq", "attr1": "food", "value1": "salad", "attr2": "sport", "value2": "football"}], "solution": {"David": {"sport": "yoga", "food": "tacos"}, "Jorge": {"sport": "football", "food": "sushi"}, "Hugo": {"sport": "basketball", "food": "salad"}}}
{"id": "bc8c67d4-ee2a-44b6-9883-e0e79f9110ae", "text_prompt": "There are 3 people: Grace, Bob, Irene.\nThe attributes are: drink: juice, tea, water; food: salad, tacos, sushi.\nClues:\n- Irene doesn't have salad.\n- Bob has juice.\n- Grace doesn't have tea.\n- Bob doesn't have tacos.\n- The person with tea drink doesn't have sushi food.\n- Whoever has sushi food has water drink.\n- Irene doesn't have juice.\n\nDetermine which attributes correspond to each person.", "entities": ["Grace", "Bob", "Irene"], "attributes": {"drink": ["juice", "tea", "water"], "food": ["salad", "tacos", "sushi"]}, "clues": [{"type": "eq", "entity": "Bob", "attr": "drink", "value": "juice"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Grace", "attr": "drink", "value": "tea"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Irene", "attr": "food", "value": "salad"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Irene", "attr": "drink", "value": "juice"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Bob", "attr": "food", "value": "tacos"}, {"type": "cross_neq", "attr1": "drink", "value1": "tea", "attr2": "food", "value2": "sushi"}, {"type": "cross_eq", "attr1": "food", "value1": "sushi", "attr2": "drink", "value2": "water"}], "solution": {"Grace": {"drink": "water", "food": "sushi"}, "Bob": {"drink": "juice", "food": "salad"}, "Irene": {"drink": "tea", "food": "tacos"}}}
{"id": "645ee764-c481-48e0-8207-166ce7d655a9", "text_prompt": "There are 3 people: Jorge, Grace, Carol.\nThe attributes are: color: red, purple, yellow; animal: bird, hamster, fish.\nClues:\n- Grace doesn't have yellow.\n- Grace doesn't have hamster.\n- Carol has red.\n- Whoever has hamster animal has red color.\n- Carol doesn't have yellow.\n- Whoever has yellow color has bird animal.\n- Grace doesn't have red.\n\nDetermine which attributes correspond to each person.", "entities": ["Jorge", "Grace", "Carol"], "attributes": {"color": ["red", "purple", "yellow"], "animal": ["bird", "hamster", "fish"]}, "clues": [{"type": "eq", "entity": "Carol", "attr": "color", "value": "red"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Grace", "attr": "color", "value": "yellow"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Grace", "attr": "color", "value": "red"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Carol", "attr": "color", "value": "yellow"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Grace", "attr": "animal", "value": "hamster"}, {"type": "cross_eq", "attr1": "animal", "value1": "hamster", "attr2": "color", "value2": "red"}, {"type": "cross_eq", "attr1": "color", "value1": "yellow", "attr2": "animal", "value2": "bird"}], "solution": {"Jorge": {"color": "yellow", "animal": "bird"}, "Grace": {"color": "purple", "animal": "fish"}, "Carol": {"color": "red", "animal": "hamster"}}}
{"id": "e0214dfc-c3d2-4874-9882-6d72c51a2ce9", "text_prompt": "There are 3 people: Olga, Sara, Marta.\nThe attributes are: city: London, Berlin, Madrid; drink: water, tea, juice.\nClues:\n- Sara doesn't have water.\n- Olga doesn't have juice.\n- The person with London city doesn't have tea drink.\n- Sara doesn't have Madrid.\n- Olga has Berlin.\n- Whoever has water drink has Madrid city.\n- Marta doesn't have London.\n\nDetermine which attributes correspond to each person.", "entities": ["Olga", "Sara", "Marta"], "attributes": {"city": ["London", "Berlin", "Madrid"], "drink": ["water", "tea", "juice"]}, "clues": [{"type": "eq", "entity": "Olga", "attr": "city", "value": "Berlin"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Olga", "attr": "drink", "value": "juice"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Sara", "attr": "drink", "value": "water"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Marta", "attr": "city", "value": "London"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Sara", "attr": "city", "value": "Madrid"}, {"type": "cross_neq", "attr1": "city", "value1": "London", "attr2": "drink", "value2": "tea"}, {"type": "cross_eq", "attr1": "drink", "value1": "water", "attr2": "city", "value2": "Madrid"}], "solution": {"Olga": {"city": "Berlin", "drink": "tea"}, "Sara": {"city": "London", "drink": "juice"}, "Marta": {"city": "Madrid", "drink": "water"}}}
{"id": "2c17121d-4ea4-4fef-88ab-8c9f0275aae1", "text_prompt": "There are 3 people: David, Alice, Vera.\nThe attributes are: drink: coffee, soda, juice; color: blue, green, purple.\nClues:\n- The person with soda drink doesn't have green color.\n- Vera doesn't have soda.\n- Alice doesn't have green.\n- Alice doesn't have juice.\n- Whoever has blue color has soda drink.\n- David has coffee.\n- Vera doesn't have purple.\n\nDetermine which attributes correspond to each person.", "entities": ["David", "Alice", "Vera"], "attributes": {"drink": ["coffee", "soda", "juice"], "color": ["blue", "green", "purple"]}, "clues": [{"type": "eq", "entity": "David", "attr": "drink", "value": "coffee"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Alice", "attr": "drink", "value": "juice"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Vera", "attr": "drink", "value": "soda"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Alice", "attr": "color", "value": "green"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Vera", "attr": "color", "value": "purple"}, {"type": "cross_neq", "attr1": "drink", "value1": "soda", "attr2": "color", "value2": "green"}, {"type": "cross_eq", "attr1": "color", "value1": "blue", "attr2": "drink", "value2": "soda"}], "solution": {"David": {"drink": "coffee", "color": "purple"}, "Alice": {"drink": "soda", "color": "blue"}, "Vera": {"drink": "juice", "color": "green"}}}
{"id": "79e55810-98c6-48e2-a01c-6cb91358bb3c", "text_prompt": "There are 3 people: Sara, David, Quinn.\nThe attributes are: city: Rome, London, Madrid; drink: juice, water, coffee.\nClues:\n- Quinn doesn't have London.\n- David doesn't have water.\n- Quinn doesn't have juice.\n- Whoever has Madrid city has coffee drink.\n- Sara has London.\n- Whoever has coffee drink has Madrid city.\n- Sara doesn't have water.\n\nDetermine which attributes correspond to each person.", "entities": ["Sara", "David", "Quinn"], "attributes": {"city": ["Rome", "London", "Madrid"], "drink": ["juice", "water", "coffee"]}, "clues": [{"type": "eq", "entity": "Sara", "attr": "city", "value": "London"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Sara", "attr": "drink", "value": "water"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Quinn", "attr": "city", "value": "London"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "David", "attr": "drink", "value": "water"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Quinn", "attr": "drink", "value": "juice"}, {"type": "cross_eq", "attr1": "drink", "value1": "coffee", "attr2": "city", "value2": "Madrid"}, {"type": "cross_eq", "attr1": "city", "value1": "Madrid", "attr2": "drink", "value2": "coffee"}], "solution": {"Sara": {"city": "London", "drink": "juice"}, "David": {"city": "Madrid", "drink": "coffee"}, "Quinn": {"city": "Rome", "drink": "water"}}}
{"id": "e994aee5-32bd-4f8a-80c6-5c61d0593bc0", "text_prompt": "There are 3 people: Eva, David, Alice.\nThe attributes are: city: Paris, Madrid, London; food: tacos, sushi, salad.\nClues:\n- Eva doesn't have salad.\n- Whoever has London city has sushi food.\n- Whoever has salad food has Paris city.\n- Eva doesn't have sushi.\n- David doesn't have London.\n- Eva doesn't have London.\n- David has Paris.\n\nDetermine which attributes correspond to each person.", "entities": ["Eva", "David", "Alice"], "attributes": {"city": ["Paris", "Madrid", "London"], "food": ["tacos", "sushi", "salad"]}, "clues": [{"type": "eq", "entity": "David", "attr": "city", "value": "Paris"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Eva", "attr": "food", "value": "salad"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "David", "attr": "city", "value": "London"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Eva", "attr": "food", "value": "sushi"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Eva", "attr": "city", "value": "London"}, {"type": "cross_eq", "attr1": "city", "value1": "London", "attr2": "food", "value2": "sushi"}, {"type": "cross_eq", "attr1": "food", "value1": "salad", "attr2": "city", "value2": "Paris"}], "solution": {"Eva": {"city": "Madrid", "food": "tacos"}, "David": {"city": "Paris", "food": "salad"}, "Alice": {"city": "London", "food": "sushi"}}}
{"id": "056ef231-7c67-44bd-a75b-9345199ee5d9", "text_prompt": "There are 3 people: Frank, Grace, Olga.\nThe attributes are: drink: juice, coffee, soda; animal: bird, cat, fish.\nClues:\n- The person with cat animal doesn't have coffee drink.\n- Olga doesn't have coffee.\n- Whoever has coffee drink has fish animal.\n- Grace doesn't have bird.\n- Olga doesn't have fish.\n- Olga has juice.\n- Olga doesn't have bird.\n\nDetermine which attributes correspond to each person.", "entities": ["Frank", "Grace", "Olga"], "attributes": {"drink": ["juice", "coffee", "soda"], "animal": ["bird", "cat", "fish"]}, "clues": [{"type": "eq", "entity": "Olga", "attr": "drink", "value": "juice"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Grace", "attr": "animal", "value": "bird"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Olga", "attr": "animal", "value": "bird"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Olga", "attr": "animal", "value": "fish"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Olga", "attr": "drink", "value": "coffee"}, {"type": "cross_neq", "attr1": "animal", "value1": "cat", "attr2": "drink", "value2": "coffee"}, {"type": "cross_eq", "attr1": "drink", "value1": "coffee", "attr2": "animal", "value2": "fish"}], "solution": {"Frank": {"drink": "soda", "animal": "bird"}, "Grace": {"drink": "coffee", "animal": "fish"}, "Olga": {"drink": "juice", "animal": "cat"}}}
{"id": "3aba63bc-3bf1-42db-beb9-c8d50b3897cd", "text_prompt": "There are 3 people: Irene, Bob, Hugo.\nThe attributes are: color: yellow, green, purple; animal: fish, hamster, dog.\nClues:\n- Irene doesn't have yellow.\n- Irene doesn't have dog.\n- Irene doesn't have green.\n- Hugo doesn't have purple.\n- The person with purple color doesn't have fish animal.\n- Whoever has dog animal has green color.\n- Bob has fish.\n\nDetermine which attributes correspond to each person.", "entities": ["Irene", "Bob", "Hugo"], "attributes": {"color": ["yellow", "green", "purple"], "animal": ["fish", "hamster", "dog"]}, "clues": [{"type": "eq", "entity": "Bob", "attr": "animal", "value": "fish"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Irene", "attr": "animal", "value": "dog"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Irene", "attr": "color", "value": "yellow"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Irene", "attr": "color", "value": "green"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Hugo", "attr": "color", "value": "purple"}, {"type": "cross_neq", "attr1": "color", "value1": "purple", "attr2": "animal", "value2": "fish"}, {"type": "cross_eq", "attr1": "animal", "value1": "dog", "attr2": "color", "value2": "green"}], "solution": {"Irene": {"color": "purple", "animal": "hamster"}, "Bob": {"color": "yellow", "animal": "fish"}, "Hugo": {"color": "green", "animal": "dog"}}}
{"id": "0d6b7ddb-982f-4606-b015-52131447e70f", "text_prompt": "There are 3 people: David, Eva, Olga.\nThe attributes are: animal: fish, hamster, dog; drink: tea, water, soda.\nClues:\n- David doesn't have fish.\n- David doesn't have soda.\n- The person with water drink doesn't have dog animal.\n- Olga has tea.\n- Olga doesn't have water.\n- David doesn't have tea.\n- Whoever has dog animal has tea drink.\n\nDetermine which attributes correspond to each person.", "entities": ["David", "Eva", "Olga"], "attributes": {"animal": ["fish", "hamster", "dog"], "drink": ["tea", "water", "soda"]}, "clues": [{"type": "eq", "entity": "Olga", "attr": "drink", "value": "tea"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Olga", "attr": "drink", "value": "water"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "David", "attr": "animal", "value": "fish"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "David", "attr": "drink", "value": "soda"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "David", "attr": "drink", "value": "tea"}, {"type": "cross_neq", "attr1": "drink", "value1": "water", "attr2": "animal", "value2": "dog"}, {"type": "cross_eq", "attr1": "animal", "value1": "dog", "attr2": "drink", "value2": "tea"}], "solution": {"David": {"animal": "hamster", "drink": "water"}, "Eva": {"animal": "fish", "drink": "soda"}, "Olga": {"animal": "dog", "drink": "tea"}}}
{"id": "b1ff3355-c82a-4855-a734-7f19b419cf8c", "text_prompt": "There are 3 people: Pablo, Vera, Quinn.\nThe attributes are: drink: soda, juice, tea; color: purple, yellow, red.\nClues:\n- Quinn doesn't have juice.\n- Pablo has juice.\n- Whoever has red color has soda drink.\n- Vera doesn't have soda.\n- Whoever has tea drink has yellow color.\n- Vera doesn't have purple.\n- Pablo doesn't have soda.\n\nDetermine which attributes correspond to each person.", "entities": ["Pablo", "Vera", "Quinn"], "attributes": {"drink": ["soda", "juice", "tea"], "color": ["purple", "yellow", "red"]}, "clues": [{"type": "eq", "entity": "Pablo", "attr": "drink", "value": "juice"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Pablo", "attr": "drink", "value": "soda"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Vera", "attr": "color", "value": "purple"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Vera", "attr": "drink", "value": "soda"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Quinn", "attr": "drink", "value": "juice"}, {"type": "cross_eq", "attr1": "drink", "value1": "tea", "attr2": "color", "value2": "yellow"}, {"type": "cross_eq", "attr1": "color", "value1": "red", "attr2": "drink", "value2": "soda"}], "solution": {"Pablo": {"drink": "juice", "color": "purple"}, "Vera": {"drink": "tea", "color": "yellow"}, "Quinn": {"drink": "soda", "color": "red"}}}
{"id": "7135f401-3dd0-4a88-aa64-fc82a47b7300", "text_prompt": "There are 3 people: David, Carol, Quinn.\nThe attributes are: sport: swimming, yoga, basketball; animal: cat, bird, dog.\nClues:\n- The person with yoga sport doesn't have dog animal.\n- Quinn doesn't have basketball.\n- Whoever has dog animal has swimming sport.\n- David doesn't have basketball.\n- David has dog.\n- Quinn doesn't have cat.\n- David doesn't have bird.\n\nDetermine which attributes correspond to each person.", "entities": ["David", "Carol", "Quinn"], "attributes": {"sport": ["swimming", "yoga", "basketball"], "animal": ["cat", "bird", "dog"]}, "clues": [{"type": "eq", "entity": "David", "attr": "animal", "value": "dog"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "David", "attr": "sport", "value": "basketball"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "David", "attr": "animal", "value": "bird"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Quinn", "attr": "sport", "value": "basketball"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Quinn", "attr": "animal", "value": "cat"}, {"type": "cross_eq", "attr1": "animal", "value1": "dog", "attr2": "sport", "value2": "swimming"}, {"type": "cross_neq", "attr1": "sport", "value1": "yoga", "attr2": "animal", "value2": "dog"}], "solution": {"David": {"sport": "swimming", "animal": "dog"}, "Carol": {"sport": "basketball", "animal": "cat"}, "Quinn": {"sport": "yoga", "animal": "bird"}}}
{"id": "d563e746-a0ae-4b8e-adc7-e3c956bd0b30", "text_prompt": "There are 3 people: Alice, Olga, Irene.\nThe attributes are: animal: cat, fish, hamster; sport: tennis, swimming, yoga.\nClues:\n- Irene has fish.\n- Whoever has swimming sport has hamster animal.\n- Irene doesn't have yoga.\n- Alice doesn't have hamster.\n- Olga doesn't have tennis.\n- The person with hamster animal doesn't have yoga sport.\n- Alice doesn't have swimming.\n\nDetermine which attributes correspond to each person.", "entities": ["Alice", "Olga", "Irene"], "attributes": {"animal": ["cat", "fish", "hamster"], "sport": ["tennis", "swimming", "yoga"]}, "clues": [{"type": "eq", "entity": "Irene", "attr": "animal", "value": "fish"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Alice", "attr": "animal", "value": "hamster"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Olga", "attr": "sport", "value": "tennis"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Irene", "attr": "sport", "value": "yoga"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Alice", "attr": "sport", "value": "swimming"}, {"type": "cross_neq", "attr1": "animal", "value1": "hamster", "attr2": "sport", "value2": "yoga"}, {"type": "cross_eq", "attr1": "sport", "value1": "swimming", "attr2": "animal", "value2": "hamster"}], "solution": {"Alice": {"animal": "cat", "sport": "yoga"}, "Olga": {"animal": "hamster", "sport": "swimming"}, "Irene": {"animal": "fish", "sport": "tennis"}}}
{"id": "dc298b0d-cfae-4458-9d19-5a6a182a3f13", "text_prompt": "There are 3 people: Marta, David, Bob.\nThe attributes are: food: pizza, sushi, salad; city: Paris, Rome, London.\nClues:\n- Bob doesn't have Paris.\n- David doesn't have sushi.\n- Marta doesn't have Paris.\n- Bob has London.\n- The person with pizza food doesn't have Paris city.\n- Marta doesn't have sushi.\n- The person with Rome city doesn't have salad food.\n\nDetermine which attributes correspond to each person.", "entities": ["Marta", "David", "Bob"], "attributes": {"food": ["pizza", "sushi", "salad"], "city": ["Paris", "Rome", "London"]}, "clues": [{"type": "eq", "entity": "Bob", "attr": "city", "value": "London"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Bob", "attr": "city", "value": "Paris"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Marta", "attr": "city", "value": "Paris"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Marta", "attr": "food", "value": "sushi"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "David", "attr": "food", "value": "sushi"}, {"type": "cross_neq", "attr1": "food", "value1": "pizza", "attr2": "city", "value2": "Paris"}, {"type": "cross_neq", "attr1": "city", "value1": "Rome", "attr2": "food", "value2": "salad"}], "solution": {"Marta": {"food": "pizza", "city": "Rome"}, "David": {"food": "salad", "city": "Paris"}, "Bob": {"food": "sushi", "city": "London"}}}
{"id": "fd1ccaa6-827a-464b-955d-55868aa11374", "text_prompt": "There are 3 people: Grace, Eva, Jorge.\nThe attributes are: animal: fish, cat, hamster; color: green, purple, yellow.\nClues:\n- The person with fish animal doesn't have yellow color.\n- Eva doesn't have cat.\n- Eva doesn't have green.\n- Grace doesn't have yellow.\n- Whoever has green color has cat animal.\n- Grace doesn't have hamster.\n- Grace has purple.\n\nDetermine which attributes correspond to each person.", "entities": ["Grace", "Eva", "Jorge"], "attributes": {"animal": ["fish", "cat", "hamster"], "color": ["green", "purple", "yellow"]}, "clues": [{"type": "eq", "entity": "Grace", "attr": "color", "value": "purple"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Eva", "attr": "color", "value": "green"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Eva", "attr": "animal", "value": "cat"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Grace", "attr": "animal", "value": "hamster"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Grace", "attr": "color", "value": "yellow"}, {"type": "cross_neq", "attr1": "animal", "value1": "fish", "attr2": "color", "value2": "yellow"}, {"type": "cross_eq", "attr1": "color", "value1": "green", "attr2": "animal", "value2": "cat"}], "solution": {"Grace": {"animal": "fish", "color": "purple"}, "Eva": {"animal": "hamster", "color": "yellow"}, "Jorge": {"animal": "cat", "color": "green"}}}
{"id": "a7ade2ff-c233-4947-b44e-0b661c2e28c5", "text_prompt": "There are 3 people: Pablo, Jorge, David.\nThe attributes are: sport: tennis, football, basketball; animal: fish, bird, hamster.\nClues:\n- Whoever has bird animal has tennis sport.\n- Pablo doesn't have basketball.\n- The person with tennis sport doesn't have hamster animal.\n- Pablo doesn't have hamster.\n- Pablo doesn't have football.\n- David has fish.\n- David doesn't have basketball.\n\nDetermine which attributes correspond to each person.", "entities": ["Pablo", "Jorge", "David"], "attributes": {"sport": ["tennis", "football", "basketball"], "animal": ["fish", "bird", "hamster"]}, "clues": [{"type": "eq", "entity": "David", "attr": "animal", "value": "fish"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Pablo", "attr": "sport", "value": "football"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Pablo", "attr": "animal", "value": "hamster"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "David", "attr": "sport", "value": "basketball"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Pablo", "attr": "sport", "value": "basketball"}, {"type": "cross_eq", "attr1": "animal", "value1": "bird", "attr2": "sport", "value2": "tennis"}, {"type": "cross_neq", "attr1": "sport", "value1": "tennis", "attr2": "animal", "value2": "hamster"}], "solution": {"Pablo": {"sport": "tennis", "animal": "bird"}, "Jorge": {"sport": "basketball", "animal": "hamster"}, "David": {"sport": "football", "animal": "fish"}}}
{"id": "815c2da3-e96d-40a2-a8e4-16dba40adcd8", "text_prompt": "There are 3 people: Irene, Bob, Jorge.\nThe attributes are: color: red, blue, yellow; drink: coffee, soda, water.\nClues:\n- Irene doesn't have yellow.\n- Bob has soda.\n- Whoever has soda drink has yellow color.\n- Bob doesn't have blue.\n- Jorge doesn't have red.\n- Jorge doesn't have water.\n- Whoever has yellow color has soda drink.\n\nDetermine which attributes correspond to each person.", "entities": ["Irene", "Bob", "Jorge"], "attributes": {"color": ["red", "blue", "yellow"], "drink": ["coffee", "soda", "water"]}, "clues": [{"type": "eq", "entity": "Bob", "attr": "drink", "value": "soda"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Jorge", "attr": "drink", "value": "water"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Bob", "attr": "color", "value": "blue"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Irene", "attr": "color", "value": "yellow"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Jorge", "attr": "color", "value": "red"}, {"type": "cross_eq", "attr1": "color", "value1": "yellow", "attr2": "drink", "value2": "soda"}, {"type": "cross_eq", "attr1": "drink", "value1": "soda", "attr2": "color", "value2": "yellow"}], "solution": {"Irene": {"color": "red", "drink": "water"}, "Bob": {"color": "yellow", "drink": "soda"}, "Jorge": {"color": "blue", "drink": "coffee"}}}
{"id": "84076e5a-e2d4-4974-b98c-3d49a32a0f4b", "text_prompt": "There are 3 people: Hugo, Frank, David.\nThe attributes are: city: Rome, Madrid, Berlin; animal: cat, bird, hamster.\nClues:\n- Whoever has Madrid city has cat animal.\n- Frank doesn't have Rome.\n- David doesn't have cat.\n- Frank has cat.\n- David doesn't have Rome.\n- Whoever has cat animal has Madrid city.\n- Hugo doesn't have hamster.\n\nDetermine which attributes correspond to each person.", "entities": ["Hugo", "Frank", "David"], "attributes": {"city": ["Rome", "Madrid", "Berlin"], "animal": ["cat", "bird", "hamster"]}, "clues": [{"type": "eq", "entity": "Frank", "attr": "animal", "value": "cat"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "David", "attr": "animal", "value": "cat"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Hugo", "attr": "animal", "value": "hamster"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Frank", "attr": "city", "value": "Rome"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "David", "attr": "city", "value": "Rome"}, {"type": "cross_eq", "attr1": "city", "value1": "Madrid", "attr2": "animal", "value2": "cat"}, {"type": "cross_eq", "attr1": "animal", "value1": "cat", "attr2": "city", "value2": "Madrid"}], "solution": {"Hugo": {"city": "Rome", "animal": "bird"}, "Frank": {"city": "Madrid", "animal": "cat"}, "David": {"city": "Berlin", "animal": "hamster"}}}
{"id": "66866327-029c-42bf-bc6d-5fe55c109edb", "text_prompt": "There are 3 people: Bob, Carol, Grace.\nThe attributes are: drink: coffee, soda, juice; sport: yoga, swimming, football.\nClues:\n- Bob doesn't have coffee.\n- Grace doesn't have coffee.\n- The person with coffee drink doesn't have swimming sport.\n- Whoever has swimming sport has juice drink.\n- Bob doesn't have juice.\n- Bob doesn't have football.\n- Bob has yoga.\n\nDetermine which attributes correspond to each person.", "entities": ["Bob", "Carol", "Grace"], "attributes": {"drink": ["coffee", "soda", "juice"], "sport": ["yoga", "swimming", "football"]}, "clues": [{"type": "eq", "entity": "Bob", "attr": "sport", "value": "yoga"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Bob", "attr": "drink", "value": "juice"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Bob", "attr": "sport", "value": "football"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Grace", "attr": "drink", "value": "coffee"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Bob", "attr": "drink", "value": "coffee"}, {"type": "cross_neq", "attr1": "drink", "value1": "coffee", "attr2": "sport", "value2": "swimming"}, {"type": "cross_eq", "attr1": "sport", "value1": "swimming", "attr2": "drink", "value2": "juice"}], "solution": {"Bob": {"drink": "soda", "sport": "yoga"}, "Carol": {"drink": "coffee", "sport": "football"}, "Grace": {"drink": "juice", "sport": "swimming"}}}
{"id": "971d8abc-e374-4038-a151-efdeb303c83b", "text_prompt": "There are 3 people: David, Pablo, Carol.\nThe attributes are: sport: yoga, tennis, swimming; animal: dog, fish, bird.\nClues:\n- David has swimming.\n- Whoever has fish animal has yoga sport.\n- The person with tennis sport doesn't have bird animal.\n- Carol doesn't have tennis.\n- David doesn't have tennis.\n- Pablo doesn't have fish.\n- David doesn't have dog.\n\nDetermine which attributes correspond to each person.", "entities": ["David", "Pablo", "Carol"], "attributes": {"sport": ["yoga", "tennis", "swimming"], "animal": ["dog", "fish", "bird"]}, "clues": [{"type": "eq", "entity": "David", "attr": "sport", "value": "swimming"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "David", "attr": "animal", "value": "dog"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Pablo", "attr": "animal", "value": "fish"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Carol", "attr": "sport", "value": "tennis"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "David", "attr": "sport", "value": "tennis"}, {"type": "cross_neq", "attr1": "sport", "value1": "tennis", "attr2": "animal", "value2": "bird"}, {"type": "cross_eq", "attr1": "animal", "value1": "fish", "attr2": "sport", "value2": "yoga"}], "solution": {"David": {"sport": "swimming", "animal": "bird"}, "Pablo": {"sport": "tennis", "animal": "dog"}, "Carol": {"sport": "yoga", "animal": "fish"}}}
{"id": "0193a0d0-7cfc-4d43-9ea9-cd7bf219021d", "text_prompt": "There are 3 people: Sara, Quinn, Olga.\nThe attributes are: drink: juice, soda, water; color: purple, red, green.\nClues:\n- Whoever has juice drink has purple color.\n- Sara doesn't have red.\n- Olga doesn't have purple.\n- Olga doesn't have soda.\n- Whoever has purple color has juice drink.\n- Quinn doesn't have green.\n- Sara has purple.\n\nDetermine which attributes correspond to each person.", "entities": ["Sara", "Quinn", "Olga"], "attributes": {"drink": ["juice", "soda", "water"], "color": ["purple", "red", "green"]}, "clues": [{"type": "eq", "entity": "Sara", "attr": "color", "value": "purple"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Sara", "attr": "color", "value": "red"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Olga", "attr": "color", "value": "purple"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Olga", "attr": "drink", "value": "soda"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Quinn", "attr": "color", "value": "green"}, {"type": "cross_eq", "attr1": "color", "value1": "purple", "attr2": "drink", "value2": "juice"}, {"type": "cross_eq", "attr1": "drink", "value1": "juice", "attr2": "color", "value2": "purple"}], "solution": {"Sara": {"drink": "juice", "color": "purple"}, "Quinn": {"drink": "soda", "color": "red"}, "Olga": {"drink": "water", "color": "green"}}}
{"id": "1ddce7ae-8ac5-4a38-ae4e-449554525f5d", "text_prompt": "There are 3 people: David, Eva, Jorge.\nThe attributes are: city: London, Paris, Madrid; animal: cat, dog, fish.\nClues:\n- David doesn't have London.\n- David doesn't have cat.\n- Eva doesn't have cat.\n- Jorge has London.\n- David doesn't have Madrid.\n- Whoever has dog animal has Madrid city.\n- Whoever has cat animal has London city.\n\nDetermine which attributes correspond to each person.", "entities": ["David", "Eva", "Jorge"], "attributes": {"city": ["London", "Paris", "Madrid"], "animal": ["cat", "dog", "fish"]}, "clues": [{"type": "eq", "entity": "Jorge", "attr": "city", "value": "London"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "David", "attr": "animal", "value": "cat"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "David", "attr": "city", "value": "London"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Eva", "attr": "animal", "value": "cat"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "David", "attr": "city", "value": "Madrid"}, {"type": "cross_eq", "attr1": "animal", "value1": "cat", "attr2": "city", "value2": "London"}, {"type": "cross_eq", "attr1": "animal", "value1": "dog", "attr2": "city", "value2": "Madrid"}], "solution": {"David": {"city": "Paris", "animal": "fish"}, "Eva": {"city": "Madrid", "animal": "dog"}, "Jorge": {"city": "London", "animal": "cat"}}}
{"id": "46e8f836-5d6a-4786-a54e-5e7b58c1f550", "text_prompt": "There are 3 people: Hugo, Carol, Alice.\nThe attributes are: city: Rome, Madrid, Berlin; color: red, blue, green.\nClues:\n- Hugo doesn't have blue.\n- Alice has blue.\n- The person with red color doesn't have Rome city.\n- Alice doesn't have Rome.\n- Alice doesn't have Berlin.\n- Carol doesn't have red.\n- Whoever has Berlin city has red color.\n\nDetermine which attributes correspond to each person.", "entities": ["Hugo", "Carol", "Alice"], "attributes": {"city": ["Rome", "Madrid", "Berlin"], "color": ["red", "blue", "green"]}, "clues": [{"type": "eq", "entity": "Alice", "attr": "color", "value": "blue"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Alice", "attr": "city", "value": "Berlin"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Carol", "attr": "color", "value": "red"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Hugo", "attr": "color", "value": "blue"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Alice", "attr": "city", "value": "Rome"}, {"type": "cross_eq", "attr1": "city", "value1": "Berlin", "attr2": "color", "value2": "red"}, {"type": "cross_neq", "attr1": "color", "value1": "red", "attr2": "city", "value2": "Rome"}], "solution": {"Hugo": {"city": "Berlin", "color": "red"}, "Carol": {"city": "Rome", "color": "green"}, "Alice": {"city": "Madrid", "color": "blue"}}}
{"id": "cd09de78-0133-4ad1-92c4-2444b467f5eb", "text_prompt": "There are 3 people: Irene, Bob, Nico.\nThe attributes are: color: blue, green, yellow; city: Paris, Rome, Berlin.\nClues:\n- Nico doesn't have blue.\n- Nico doesn't have yellow.\n- Nico doesn't have Rome.\n- Irene has Paris.\n- Whoever has Berlin city has green color.\n- Bob doesn't have Paris.\n- The person with blue color doesn't have Rome city.\n\nDetermine which attributes correspond to each person.", "entities": ["Irene", "Bob", "Nico"], "attributes": {"color": ["blue", "green", "yellow"], "city": ["Paris", "Rome", "Berlin"]}, "clues": [{"type": "eq", "entity": "Irene", "attr": "city", "value": "Paris"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Nico", "attr": "city", "value": "Rome"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Nico", "attr": "color", "value": "blue"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Nico", "attr": "color", "value": "yellow"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Bob", "attr": "city", "value": "Paris"}, {"type": "cross_eq", "attr1": "city", "value1": "Berlin", "attr2": "color", "value2": "green"}, {"type": "cross_neq", "attr1": "color", "value1": "blue", "attr2": "city", "value2": "Rome"}], "solution": {"Irene": {"color": "blue", "city": "Paris"}, "Bob": {"color": "yellow", "city": "Rome"}, "Nico": {"color": "green", "city": "Berlin"}}}
{"id": "33f39d64-3254-42f3-a1ef-dacddd7623e0", "text_prompt": "There are 3 people: Quinn, Vera, Marta.\nThe attributes are: city: Paris, Madrid, Rome; drink: juice, water, coffee.\nClues:\n- Quinn has juice.\n- Vera doesn't have water.\n- Vera doesn't have Rome.\n- Marta doesn't have Madrid.\n- Marta doesn't have coffee.\n- Whoever has Paris city has juice drink.\n- Whoever has water drink has Rome city.\n\nDetermine which attributes correspond to each person.", "entities": ["Quinn", "Vera", "Marta"], "attributes": {"city": ["Paris", "Madrid", "Rome"], "drink": ["juice", "water", "coffee"]}, "clues": [{"type": "eq", "entity": "Quinn", "attr": "drink", "value": "juice"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Marta", "attr": "city", "value": "Madrid"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Marta", "attr": "drink", "value": "coffee"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Vera", "attr": "city", "value": "Rome"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Vera", "attr": "drink", "value": "water"}, {"type": "cross_eq", "attr1": "drink", "value1": "water", "attr2": "city", "value2": "Rome"}, {"type": "cross_eq", "attr1": "city", "value1": "Paris", "attr2": "drink", "value2": "juice"}], "solution": {"Quinn": {"city": "Paris", "drink": "juice"}, "Vera": {"city": "Madrid", "drink": "coffee"}, "Marta": {"city": "Rome", "drink": "water"}}}
{"id": "a03e7993-4bb9-4b21-b0ee-c200f27abd1c", "text_prompt": "There are 3 people: Alice, Pablo, Marta.\nThe attributes are: sport: swimming, yoga, basketball; food: pasta, tacos, sushi.\nClues:\n- Alice doesn't have pasta.\n- Pablo doesn't have sushi.\n- Marta doesn't have pasta.\n- Alice has yoga.\n- Pablo doesn't have basketball.\n- The person with sushi food doesn't have swimming sport.\n- The person with tacos food doesn't have yoga sport.\n\nDetermine which attributes correspond to each person.", "entities": ["Alice", "Pablo", "Marta"], "attributes": {"sport": ["swimming", "yoga", "basketball"], "food": ["pasta", "tacos", "sushi"]}, "clues": [{"type": "eq", "entity": "Alice", "attr": "sport", "value": "yoga"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Pablo", "attr": "sport", "value": "basketball"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Alice", "attr": "food", "value": "pasta"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Pablo", "attr": "food", "value": "sushi"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Marta", "attr": "food", "value": "pasta"}, {"type": "cross_neq", "attr1": "food", "value1": "sushi", "attr2": "sport", "value2": "swimming"}, {"type": "cross_neq", "attr1": "food", "value1": "tacos", "attr2": "sport", "value2": "yoga"}], "solution": {"Alice": {"sport": "yoga", "food": "sushi"}, "Pablo": {"sport": "swimming", "food": "pasta"}, "Marta": {"sport": "basketball", "food": "tacos"}}}
{"id": "3182ce93-6095-4014-aaa2-9a8f9f2ff14b", "text_prompt": "There are 3 people: Eva, Sara, Carol.\nThe attributes are: sport: yoga, football, tennis; city: Madrid, Rome, Berlin.\nClues:\n- Carol doesn't have football.\n- Eva doesn't have football.\n- Carol doesn't have yoga.\n- Eva doesn't have Berlin.\n- Whoever has yoga sport has Madrid city.\n- Sara has Berlin.\n- The person with Rome city doesn't have football sport.\n\nDetermine which attributes correspond to each person.", "entities": ["Eva", "Sara", "Carol"], "attributes": {"sport": ["yoga", "football", "tennis"], "city": ["Madrid", "Rome", "Berlin"]}, "clues": [{"type": "eq", "entity": "Sara", "attr": "city", "value": "Berlin"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Eva", "attr": "sport", "value": "football"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Eva", "attr": "city", "value": "Berlin"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Carol", "attr": "sport", "value": "yoga"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Carol", "attr": "sport", "value": "football"}, {"type": "cross_neq", "attr1": "city", "value1": "Rome", "attr2": "sport", "value2": "football"}, {"type": "cross_eq", "attr1": "sport", "value1": "yoga", "attr2": "city", "value2": "Madrid"}], "solution": {"Eva": {"sport": "yoga", "city": "Madrid"}, "Sara": {"sport": "football", "city": "Berlin"}, "Carol": {"sport": "tennis", "city": "Rome"}}}
{"id": "475ba0d8-0d67-4a07-94eb-7fcb5868d656", "text_prompt": "There are 3 people: Vera, Hugo, Alice.\nThe attributes are: food: pizza, sushi, pasta; animal: cat, bird, hamster.\nClues:\n- Hugo doesn't have bird.\n- Vera doesn't have pizza.\n- Whoever has bird animal has sushi food.\n- Vera has bird.\n- Alice doesn't have pasta.\n- Alice doesn't have hamster.\n- The person with pizza food doesn't have bird animal.\n\nDetermine which attributes correspond to each person.", "entities": ["Vera", "Hugo", "Alice"], "attributes": {"food": ["pizza", "sushi", "pasta"], "animal": ["cat", "bird", "hamster"]}, "clues": [{"type": "eq", "entity": "Vera", "attr": "animal", "value": "bird"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Alice", "attr": "animal", "value": "hamster"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Hugo", "attr": "animal", "value": "bird"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Alice", "attr": "food", "value": "pasta"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Vera", "attr": "food", "value": "pizza"}, {"type": "cross_neq", "attr1": "food", "value1": "pizza", "attr2": "animal", "value2": "bird"}, {"type": "cross_eq", "attr1": "animal", "value1": "bird", "attr2": "food", "value2": "sushi"}], "solution": {"Vera": {"food": "sushi", "animal": "bird"}, "Hugo": {"food": "pasta", "animal": "hamster"}, "Alice": {"food": "pizza", "animal": "cat"}}}
{"id": "a2b9cf79-4210-447c-bef6-708cfc11be9d", "text_prompt": "There are 3 people: Vera, Carol, Jorge.\nThe attributes are: food: sushi, pasta, salad; sport: football, tennis, swimming.\nClues:\n- Jorge has salad.\n- Jorge doesn't have swimming.\n- Jorge doesn't have tennis.\n- Whoever has sushi food has tennis sport.\n- Whoever has swimming sport has pasta food.\n- Vera doesn't have pasta.\n- Carol doesn't have tennis.\n\nDetermine which attributes correspond to each person.", "entities": ["Vera", "Carol", "Jorge"], "attributes": {"food": ["sushi", "pasta", "salad"], "sport": ["football", "tennis", "swimming"]}, "clues": [{"type": "eq", "entity": "Jorge", "attr": "food", "value": "salad"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Jorge", "attr": "sport", "value": "swimming"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Carol", "attr": "sport", "value": "tennis"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Vera", "attr": "food", "value": "pasta"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Jorge", "attr": "sport", "value": "tennis"}, {"type": "cross_eq", "attr1": "food", "value1": "sushi", "attr2": "sport", "value2": "tennis"}, {"type": "cross_eq", "attr1": "sport", "value1": "swimming", "attr2": "food", "value2": "pasta"}], "solution": {"Vera": {"food": "sushi", "sport": "tennis"}, "Carol": {"food": "pasta", "sport": "swimming"}, "Jorge": {"food": "salad", "sport": "football"}}}
{"id": "bc1ce69b-d51a-48d1-b6c2-267390f1e175", "text_prompt": "There are 3 people: Alice, Bob, David.\nThe attributes are: city: Madrid, Paris, Berlin; sport: yoga, basketball, swimming.\nClues:\n- Whoever has yoga sport has Madrid city.\n- Whoever has Paris city has swimming sport.\n- David doesn't have Madrid.\n- Bob doesn't have swimming.\n- Bob has Berlin.\n- Alice doesn't have Berlin.\n- Alice doesn't have basketball.\n\nDetermine which attributes correspond to each person.", "entities": ["Alice", "Bob", "David"], "attributes": {"city": ["Madrid", "Paris", "Berlin"], "sport": ["yoga", "basketball", "swimming"]}, "clues": [{"type": "eq", "entity": "Bob", "attr": "city", "value": "Berlin"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Alice", "attr": "sport", "value": "basketball"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Alice", "attr": "city", "value": "Berlin"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Bob", "attr": "sport", "value": "swimming"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "David", "attr": "city", "value": "Madrid"}, {"type": "cross_eq", "attr1": "city", "value1": "Paris", "attr2": "sport", "value2": "swimming"}, {"type": "cross_eq", "attr1": "sport", "value1": "yoga", "attr2": "city", "value2": "Madrid"}], "solution": {"Alice": {"city": "Madrid", "sport": "yoga"}, "Bob": {"city": "Berlin", "sport": "basketball"}, "David": {"city": "Paris", "sport": "swimming"}}}
{"id": "545a02ba-df3e-4a76-940d-60793cdc61a4", "text_prompt": "There are 3 people: Eva, Vera, Olga.\nThe attributes are: sport: football, tennis, basketball; color: green, red, yellow.\nClues:\n- Vera doesn't have green.\n- Vera has tennis.\n- The person with tennis sport doesn't have red color.\n- Olga doesn't have football.\n- Olga doesn't have red.\n- Olga doesn't have yellow.\n- The person with yellow color doesn't have basketball sport.\n\nDetermine which attributes correspond to each person.", "entities": ["Eva", "Vera", "Olga"], "attributes": {"sport": ["football", "tennis", "basketball"], "color": ["green", "red", "yellow"]}, "clues": [{"type": "eq", "entity": "Vera", "attr": "sport", "value": "tennis"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Olga", "attr": "color", "value": "red"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Vera", "attr": "color", "value": "green"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Olga", "attr": "sport", "value": "football"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Olga", "attr": "color", "value": "yellow"}, {"type": "cross_neq", "attr1": "color", "value1": "yellow", "attr2": "sport", "value2": "basketball"}, {"type": "cross_neq", "attr1": "sport", "value1": "tennis", "attr2": "color", "value2": "red"}], "solution": {"Eva": {"sport": "football", "color": "red"}, "Vera": {"sport": "tennis", "color": "yellow"}, "Olga": {"sport": "basketball", "color": "green"}}}
{"id": "52c7eaa5-90d4-48fc-b61c-619f8b75ba7b", "text_prompt": "There are 3 people: Eva, Irene, Pablo.\nThe attributes are: animal: cat, dog, bird; drink: soda, juice, water.\nClues:\n- Eva has water.\n- Whoever has soda drink has cat animal.\n- Whoever has water drink has dog animal.\n- Eva doesn't have juice.\n- Pablo doesn't have dog.\n- Eva doesn't have bird.\n- Pablo doesn't have soda.\n\nDetermine which attributes correspond to each person.", "entities": ["Eva", "Irene", "Pablo"], "attributes": {"animal": ["cat", "dog", "bird"], "drink": ["soda", "juice", "water"]}, "clues": [{"type": "eq", "entity": "Eva", "attr": "drink", "value": "water"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Eva", "attr": "drink", "value": "juice"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Eva", "attr": "animal", "value": "bird"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Pablo", "attr": "drink", "value": "soda"}, {"type": "neq", "entity": "Pablo", "attr": "animal", "value": "dog"}, {"type": "cross_eq", "attr1": "drink", "value1": "water", "attr2": "animal", "value2": "dog"}, {"type": "cross_eq", "attr1": "drink", "value1": "soda", "attr2": "animal", "value2": "cat"}], "solution": {"Eva": {"animal": "dog", "drink": "water"}, "Irene": {"animal": "cat", "drink": "soda"}, "Pablo": {"animal": "bird", "drink": "juice"}}}
